字幕来自网络
调校｜lx520@字幕库(www.zimuku.net)
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
游说是深谋远虑的博弈
Lobbying is about foresight.
需关注对手的行为
About anticipating your opponent's moves
并作出相应对策
and devising countermeasures.
能够预见对方手牌
The winner plots one step ahead of the opposition,
静待其出牌之后
and plays her trump card
亮出王牌者 为王
just after they play theirs.
在法庭上
You better not be saying that
最好不要说这样的话
when you're in there.
要攻其不备 出其不意
It's about making sure you surprise them,
而不是被对方乱了方寸
and they don't surprise you.
我再问一遍
I'm gonna ask you again.
斯隆女士 可否
Miss Sloane, could you please
描述一下你的工作性质？
describe the nature of your work?
鉴于法律顾问的建议
On the advice of counsel,
恕我无法回答你的问题
I respectfully decline to answer your question,
根据美国宪法第五修正案
based on my rights under the Fifth Amendment
我有权保持沉默
to the United States Constitution.
这几句话
Those words,
当你在完成宣誓 确认细节时
when you're not taking the oath or confirming details,
每句话都会成为呈堂证供
those words, in that order, are all you're gonna say.
“通常来说 你是否承认自己
"On average, would you say you bribed public officials
“基本每个月都会有贿赂公职官员的行为？”
"more or less than once a month?"
鉴于法律顾问的建议… 我打断一下
Upon the advice of counsel... Can I deviate slightly?
“鉴于法律顾问”？还是可以说…
"On the advice of counsel"? On the advice
- “鉴于我的辩护律师”？ - 不可以…
- "of my attorney"?  - You do not...
好吧我懂了 这么称呼
Okay, okay, I understand that last one's
对你来说风险太大
too adventurous for you.
把第五修正案常常挂在嘴边
This would be a whole lot easier
岂不是更容易吗
if I could just shout "Fifth."
他们想送你进大牢
They want you behind bars.
只要你发出一句声明
You make one statement,
要为自己澄清罪行
you correct one nefarious allegation,
那你就废废了
that's it.
丢掉了第五法案赋予你的权利
You waive your right to the Fifth
还不得不面对各种各样的问题
and you're compelled to answer everything.
他们会在全国媒体面前
They're taking you to the woodshed
把你拉下水
in front of the national press.
会不断激怒你
They're gonna rile you so bad
就连甘地也会气得不行
they'd make Gandhi wanna cut their tongues out.
“你是否安排过类似旅行
"Did you arrange for benefits such as travel,
“豪华住宿
"luxury accommodations,
“比赛门票之类 并从中获利
"and sports tickets to be furnished
“给国会成员
"to members of Congress
“而且是受委托人的要求？”
"at the behest of your clients?"
“你是否安排过类似旅行
"Did you arrange for benefits such as travel,
“豪华住宿 比赛门票之类…”
"luxury accommodations, and sports tickets to..."
丹尼尔 我出庭时
Daniel. When I take the stand,
什么都不会说
you'll see nothing but a granite wall.
很好
Good.
[华盛顿 美国国会 4月18日]
斯隆女士！
Miss Sloane!
无可奉告 谢谢
Nothing to say, guys, thank you.
斯隆女士 斯隆女士！
Miss Sloane, Miss Sloane!
真挤
This is tight.
你还认为他们会选择一个更合适的场合
You'd think they would choose a more appropriate venue.
看来国会还是想要占领主动啊
Well, turns out the Nationals had a home game.
[媒体席]
[参议员 斯珀林]
早
Good morning.
我是参议员 罗纳德·斯珀林
I am Senator Ronald Sperling,
本次庭审主席 斯隆女士
Chair of this Hearing. Miss Sloane...
请举起右手
Please raise your right hand.
[美国参议院四号会议室]
你愿意发誓 所述之言纯属实言
Do you solemnly swear that you will tell the truth,
并且无任何隐瞒
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth,
愿受谎言的惩罚吗？
under pains and penalties of perjury?
- 我愿意  - 请坐
- I do.  - Please, sit.
请证人陈述自己的全名
Will the witness please state her full name
以供法庭记录
for the record?
玛德琳·伊丽莎白·斯隆
Madeline Elizabeth Sloane.
请大点声
Louder, please.
玛德琳·伊丽莎白·斯隆
Madeline Elizabeth Sloane.
请证人确认
And could the witness please confirm
这些信息是否准确
that these details are accurate...
嗯…
Uh...
一九七六年七月二十六生人
Date of birth, July 26, 1976, address...
住址是华盛顿新罕布什尔州大道西北七百号
Suite 504, Watergate South,
水门南公寓 五〇四号套房？
700 New Hampshire Avenue North West, Washington D.C.?
是的
Correct.
从二〇〇六年到二〇一六年的这十年时间里
You were employed by Cole, Kravitz and Waterman LLP
你曾在科尔 克拉维茨和沃特曼合伙公司工作
for a 10-year period between 2006 and 2016,
在此之前…
before moving on earlier...
是十一年
Eleven year period.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
二〇〇六年到二〇一六年 是十一年
There are 11 years between 2006 and 2016.
你在该公司工作时
What was the nature of your work
工作性质是如何的？
with Cole, Kravitz and Waterman LLP?
鉴于法律顾问的建议
Upon the advice of counsel,
恕我无法回答你的问题
I must respectfully decline to answer your question,
根据美国宪法第五修正案
based on my rights under the Fifth Amendment
我有权保持沉默
to the United States Constitution.
在去年的十月十二日
Did you, October 12th of last year,
你是否
accept as a client the government
就向美国境内进口棕榈油一事
of the Asian Republic of Indonesia,
为反抗额外的联邦关税征收
for the purpose of campaigning against
接受成为
the levy of additional Federal duties
亚洲印度尼西亚共和国政府委托人？
on the importation of palm oil into the United States?
鉴于法律顾问的建议
Upon the advice of counsel,
恕我无法回答你的问题
I must respectfully decline to answer your question,
根据美国宪法第五修正案
based on my rights under the Fifth Amendment
我有权保持沉默
to the United States Constitution.
[十三周前]
今天是有意义的一天 知道为什么吗？
Today is a landmark day, you know why?
因为我解放了
Because I'm free.
那你说说 有什么今天可以
Name one thing you can do today
但昨天不能做的事情
that you couldn't have done yesterday.
辞职
Quit my job.
你昨天也可以辞职
You could've done that yesterday,
但会让你看起来蠢爆了
but it would've been stupid.
- 我可以今天辞职…  - 还是很蠢
- I can quit today and...  - It'd still be stupid.
你刚还清大学时欠下的债
You clear your college debt
就欢天喜地打算读研究生了？
and celebrate by enrolling in post-grad?
我更爱学术
Academia's more my scene.
我知道你快要解放心情昂扬
You didn't follow me into the crapper
但也不至于跟我跟到厕所里来吧 简
to gloat about freedom, Jane.
跟我说说“能多益税”的事吧
Talk to me about the Nutella Tax.
真的要这么叫吗？
Uh, we're really calling it the "Nutella Tax"?
棕榈油是能多益里的关键成分
Palm oil is a key ingredient in Nutella.
如果联邦政府要收取棕榈油百分之三百的税
If the Federal Government taxes it at 300%,
我们的损失就更多了
it'll cost more for us to gorge ourselves on it.
棕榈油不是哪里都会用到吗？
Isn't palm oil in pretty much everything?
我们本也可以管这个叫肥皂税的
We could have called it the Soap Tax,
但是相比肥皂
but the public cares more about Nutella
公众还是对能多益更感兴趣
than they do soap.
不管怎样 我们又多了四位
Anyway, we get four more senators
反对这个法案的参议员
to come out against the bill,
撤回法案的事情 就全靠雅各布斯了
we can lean on Jacobs to withdraw it.
你打算怎么做？
What are you gonna do?
让印尼那边带参议员雅各布斯
Tell the Indonesians they're going to host Senator Jacobs
去种植园实地考察下
on a field trip to one of their plantations.
你便后从来不洗手
You never washed your hands.
他会带老婆孩子去热带疯玩一圈
He'll take the wife and kids on a tropical vacation.
带着好消息回来
Come back hailing their conservation efforts.
这法案就被我们搞定了
His bill dies a quiet death.
如果是印尼政府买单
If the Indonesian government pays for it,
这就是违法的
it's illegal.
如果他们利用非营利组织赞助这次旅行
If they use a non-profit LLP to sponsor the travel,
那么这就完全合法了
it's perfectly legal.
因为这样旅行就变成一次教育考察了
As long as the trip is for educational purposes.
但实际上还是印尼政府买的单
But, the Indonesian government is still paying for it.
你看 这就是我打算读研究生的原因
See, this is why I'm thinking about post-grad.
简 人们读书 是要为进入现实世界做准备
Jane, we go to school to prepare us for the real world.
我可能并不喜欢现实世界
I'm not sure I like the real world.
你就喜欢把自己埋在苏格拉底的书堆里吗？
So you want to bury your head in Socrates?
其实 那些都不是苏格拉底写的
You know that Socrates never actually wrote anything.
我们跑题了
That's beside the point.
不喜欢的话 就做出改变
If you don't like it, you change it.
- 这就是你工作的意义  - 斯隆女士！
- That's why you're here.  - Miss Sloane!
他们已经在会议室等您了
They're ready for you in the conference room.
斯潘塞 你知道相比肥皂
Hey, Spencer, did you know that Americans care more
能多益更关心能多益吗？
about Nutella than they do about soap?
好吧
Uh, okay.
看见没？
See that?
毫无反应
No reaction.
各位 我们速战速决
Okay, guys, we gotta be quick this morning,
我还有个会
I've got a meeting to get to.
国际货币基金组织集会大约有多少人？
How many are they expecting at the IMF rally?
五百到一千人
Between 500 and 1,000.
大约百分之百的比例？
There's a margin of 100%?
也就是说 没有人愿意出面？
Does that technically mean that nobody might show up?
至少会出席五百人 其他的就看天气咯
Five hundred's the minimum, the rest depends on weather.
看样子晴天人们不太愿意出门呢
Seems more people hate banks when the sun's out.
- 天气预报怎么说？ - 利兹？
- What's the weather forecast?  - Liz?
雅各布斯去印尼的那几天
Time we sold Jacobs on Indonesia.
我知道
I know.
- 等亨利倒台了 我们就有…  - 群聚效应 我懂
- When Henry falls we've got...  - Critical mass, I'm aware.
找个非营利组织赞助这次旅行
Get a non-profit to sponsor a vacation.
他会给脸不要脸的
They give him face and he'll pull it.
你是刚从女洗手间出来吗？
Did you just come from the ladies' room?
我不懂你的意思
Uh, I have no idea what you're talking about.
我们说的是国际货币基金组织集会的出席人数
We're talking about numbers at the IMF rally.
亚历克斯 通知麦德龙·泰兰
All right, Alex, put Metro Talent on notice,
- 我们请求支援  - 这就去
- we may need reinforcements.  - I'm on it.
真的要动用群众演员吗？
We're really gonna use movie extras?
那个叫嚣着指责企业贪婪的家伙
The guy shouting about corporate greed
站在演员选派部无业游民的身边
becomes a lot less credible standing next
举个“废除货币”标语
to a hobo from central casting,
少了不少说服力
with a banner that reads, "Abolish money."
“什么话
"Shit is fucked up
“真是一派胡言”
"and bullshit."
这标语真是赞爆了 不会是我们的人吧
Best banner at Occupy. Tell me that was one of ours.
不是 这要比我能想到的方式妙多了
Oh, no, that was creative way beyond my capabilities.
- 富兰克林！磨茹白蛋糕呢？ - 在！
- Franklin! Shmallow Cakes?  - Uh, yeah!
蛋糕和饼干都要收营业税
Does sales tax apply to cakes and cookies,
还是只是其中一种要收？
or only to one of those?
我不清楚
I don't know.
你不清楚？
You don't know?
你们听好了
All right, everybody, listen up!
我要讲故事了
I'm going to tell you a story.
可别
Please, no.
有一天 牧师从教堂
A priest is giving a young nun
开车把一位年轻修女送回家
a lift home from church one day,
他趁换档的功夫
and as he's shifting gears,
把手搭在修女的膝盖上
he rests his hand on the nun's knee.
这样太无礼了 是不对的
This is offensive and inappropriate.
年轻修女抬头看看牧师 说
The young nun looks up at the priest and says,
“神父 你还记得路加福音十四章十节吗”
"Father, remember Luke 14:10."
牧师收回了自己的手 感到尴尬
The priest withdraws his hand, embarrassed.
后来路遇红灯 车子又停下来
Next time they stop at a light,
他把手放在修女大腿上方一点点的位置
he places his hand a little higher up on her thigh,
修女又说“还记得路加福音十四章十节吗 神父”
again the nun says, "Remember Luke 14:10, Father."
牧师道了歉
The priest apologizes.
“我心有余而力不足” 他说
"The flesh is weak," he says.
把修女送回家后 牧师回到家里
So he drops her off, and when he gets home,
拿出圣经 翻到路加福音十四章十节
he reaches for his bible and he flips to Luke 14:10.
你们听懂了吗？
Anyone know what it says? Hmm?
什么意思 帕特？
What does it say, Pat?
“朋友 请上座 这样才能获得荣耀！”
"Friend, come up higher, then shalt thou have glory!"
了解自己分内的事！
Know your subject, people!
不然的话
Failure to do so may result
可能会丧失绝佳的机会
in the loss of a golden opportunity.
今天下午上班的时候
When I see you this afternoon,
最好熟练到
you'd better be ready to recite
可以用世界语背下免税代码
that tax code in Esperanto.
他们说我应该和她握手
I'm... I'm told I should offer her my hand, huh?
什么意思
How do you mean?
我是说第一次见面的时候
Well, when we meet, I'm told that
他们说她并不喜欢
she doesn't care for all that kissy-kissy stuff
一般人见面的吻面礼
that most women do these days.
你们之前没见过吗？
You two have never met?
倒是见过几面
Well, we've been to several of the same functions, yeah,
可从没互相认识过
but we've never been introduced.
这里又不大 这怎么可能呢？
In a town this small, how does that happen?
我该握手吗？
So, should I offer my hand?
不必太担心这个
I wouldn't worry about it.
- 利兹？ - 早
- Liz?  - Good morning!
比尔·桑福德
Bill Sandford.
居然这么久我们才认识
I'm amazed it's taken this long.
本来我是想
Well, you know, I wanted to introduce myself
在自由企业晚宴上就自我介绍的
at the Free Enterprise Dinner,
但你很快就离场了
but you were the first one out the door.
我去处理了下国会那边的小状况
Minor crisis on the Hill.
换做一般的领导
Well, a lesser commander
就会直接交给下属去办了
would've left that to a soldier,
这也是我拜访的原因
which is the reason I'm here.
诸位有何贵干？
Why exactly are you here?
像希顿·哈里斯一样推翻法案
Killing bills like Heaton-Harris,
对你们来说是常事
that's food and drink to you guys.
- 这么说你读过了？ - 没有 但我清楚法案的内容
- So you've read it?  - No, but I know what it is.
这是一部基于普遍背景调查的
It's a bipartisan gun bill
两党枪支法案
requiring universal background checks.
不只是针对枪支 一切轻武器都算
On all sales of firearms.
就好比说
Now, come on.
父子关系是一生连带的
A father and his son, lifelong friends.
都是早晚的事
It just means longer delays.
分析了一种独裁式的犯罪行为
It's some kind of Big Brother type criminal
建立了心理健康的数据库
and mental health database.
对于宪法第二修正案有些相悖
An unconstitutional fetter on the Second Amendment
正如你所说
which, as you said,
这是我们的常态
we will eat for breakfast.
桑福德先生 一般来说 我处理的都是些课税
Mr. Sandford, I deal primarily in taxation
和联邦政府
and Federal Government interference
对自由企业的干涉事件 这件事…
in free enterprise. This...
我清楚 我清楚
I'm aware, I am aware.
听我一句
But I'll tell you,
你为自己树立的形象
the reputation you have garnered for yourself,
吸引了我们想要与你共事
we were just looking for an excuse to engage you.
好吧 我们谈谈吧
Okay. Let's have it.
女性
Women.
投票数据表明
Our polling data is telling us
我们不只是为了和女性选民取得联系
that we're not connecting with the female voter.
也想做出些改变
So, we want to change the narrative.
母亲不再会因为枪支失去自己的孩子
From mothers losing their kids to guns,
而是可以举起枪支保护他们
to mothers protecting their kids with guns.
受虐的妻子也不会再收到子弹的威胁
From a battered wife threatened by a bullet,
而是可以依靠枪支保护自己
to fending off her violent husband with a .38.
枪支成为赋予女性权力的工具
Guns as tools of female empowerment.
那句话怎么说来着？上帝创造人类
What's the saying? God created humans...
发明改变人生
Samuel Colt made them equal.
利兹 假设有这样一个组织
Now, Liz, imagine a new organization,
专门是为那些
pitched at women who are deterred
因第二修正案止步不前的女人建立的
by the strong rhetoric of the Second Amendment groups,
由我们的参与保证了她们的政治权利
and by our association with the political right.
但不涉及我们自己
But no links to us, no baggage.
不支持蓄意储存枪支
No overt position on guns.
而你
And you
就是这个议程的负责人
will build it up, you will drive its agenda,
慢慢地 你必然
and slowly but surely,
会将这些受益人
you will turn those members
转变为第二修正案的维护者
into paid-up guardians of the Second Amendment.
所以呢？
So, what? Um...
为了安全而持枪的母亲…
Mothers For A Safer America...
一定要这样
Achieved by making sure
让每个美国人都武装到牙齿吗？
every last citizen is armed to the teeth?
利兹？
Liz?
老天 难道这就是我树立的形象吗？
Jesus, is this the reputation I've garnered?
一个徘徊在道德边缘的人？
Gold medalist in ethical limbo?
我们只是在讨论问题 上升不到道德层面吧
I see no ethical problem with reframing an issue.
只是为了迎合女性选民而支持枪支买卖
Trying to win the female vote by taking the gun lobby
还美其名曰保护女性安全
and dressing it up in a frilly pink frock,
太不成熟了
it is so crude,
这肯定是你们一帮糙老爷们想出来的怪点子
it could only have originated in a room full of old men.
并不是
Well, it didn't!
这是我自己的主义
This is my own idea.
我建议你趁早断了念想
Well, my advice is to kill it in Heaton.
事情可没有你想象的那么简单
You'll need more than the trite wisdom
我们拿安全说事
that we value security
是为了回到第二修正案的议题上
to get us behind your views on the Second Amendment.
但事实就是
Well, the fact remains
目前女性选民
that when it comes to the female voter,
给我们的回馈并不乐观
our numbers need to be better.
我知道了
I see.
这样吧 拿数据说话
Well, why don't I take a look at the numbers
我们就事论事
and then we'll proceed from there?
她认为自己是谁啊？
Who the hell does she think she is?
计划可能就此夭折
It can be spun.
为获得选民信任
For the purpose of gaining trust,
这可能是最合适的策略了
it Heaton been the right tactical move.
你信不信 那一瞬间
And do you believe, for one nanosecond,
她脑子里想的
that was at the forefront of her mind
就是要他卷铺盖
when she told him to take his business
滚出我们这里
and shove it up his gun barrel?
坎迪斯！
Candice!
叫斯隆马上来我办公室！
I want Sloane in my office now!
办事效率真是高吧
She's good, isn't she?
你想拿数据说话？
You'll look at the numbers?
我敢说
I'm sure the president
国会任何一个组织的头头
of one of the most powerful groups on the Hill
都会因女王陛下
will be honored that Her Majesty
提出要拿数据说话而感到荣幸吧！
has agreed to look at the fucking numbers!
你出了什么问题？
What's going on with you?
目前的系统很不健全
The current system is so porous, it floats.
我可不记得你以前
I don't remember you caring, ever,
关心过枪支问题
one way or another about guns!
在科隆比纳和查尔斯顿事件后
My position solidified somewhere
我就坚定了自己的立场
between Columbine and Charleston.
乔治 任何大人物
Come on, George, any head-case,
重犯 甚至是恐怖分子 都可以
felon or terrorist can buy an assault rifle
从枪展 网络
from a gun show, the Internet,
或者从保龄球馆认识的朋友那里买到冲锋枪
or his buddy at the Bowl-O-Rama
连身份证都不需要提供
without so much as an ID.
多亏了希顿·哈里斯 枪支才受到管制
Heaton-Harris puts a stop to that.
老天啊 利兹 这可是反枪支管制啊
Christ, Liz, this is the gun lobby.
你知不知道
Do you have any idea
我把他们劝进来花了多少心血？
how long I've been trying to reel them in?
我知道了
No.
肯定有事
Something happened.
一定是你认识的什么人是枪支暴力的受害者
Someone you know was the victim of a gun crime.
不是 这就是我的观念
Nonsense. I just formed an opinion.
你是自由市场的冠军
You're the champion of the free market.
你痛恨那些不痛不痒的政府干预
You abhor frivolous government intervention...
我甚至觉得
I would hardly categorize
枪支法丝毫不无道理
responsible gun laws as frivolous...
印尼人！
Indonesians!
老天 你居然代表印尼人的立场！
For Christ's sake, you rep Indonesians!
我们不能让政府浑水摸鱼
To stop our government from looting
取走他们的经济来源
one of their few sources of income.
印尼怎么了？
And what is wrong with Indonesia?
我们不还要护送阿尔·雅各布斯
We're about to secure Al Jacobs
在那边考察么
with a field trip there.
你这算是承诺还是威胁？
Is that a promise or a threat?
我脑中甚至浮现出一位优秀的参议员
I can just picture the good Senator
被土著人丢到大锅里
being boiled in a cauldron
围跳土著舞的画面
with all these natives dancing around him.
你还是管好自己的五百个委托人吧
Get back to your Fortune 500 clients.
你这样来一出是一出
Your colorful interventions are the cause of
会给我们招来大麻烦的
a lot of industry backchat this firm could do without.
我依照信念做事
I work on behalf of causes I believe in.
这样才不会寝食难安
That's how I sleep at night.
做我们这行的 睡觉也不能放松警惕
You don't sleep at night.
时刻考虑的都是稳赢
You sit and obsess about winning,
无论代价如何
no matter the cause.
你包里的小药片
Those little pills in your purse
不是哄你入睡的工具
are not the kind that lull you to sleep.
你和你幼稚无用的团队还能留下来
The only reason you
只是因为
and your team of gum-chewing ragamuffins are here
你傲慢的外壳或许会吸引来
is that your arrogant pranks might generate enough buzz
像比尔·桑福德这样的委托人
to attract clients like Bill Sandford.
也就是说 如果你不努力完成他的诉求
Meaning, if you don't dedicate yourself to his cause,
我们留你也无用了
this firm won't have any use for you.
去研究那些数字吧
Now go away, look into those numbers,
让女性开始对枪支感兴趣
and start getting women into guns.
- 有头晕恶心的现象吗？ - 没
- Any dizziness? Nausea?  - No.
你总是这么说
That's what you always say.
医生我没事的
Doctor, I'm fine.
如果我的保险公司不费心
If my insurance company weren't such sticklers,
我也就付不起请你的钱了
we wouldn't even be having this conversation.
你几点睡觉？
What time are you getting to sleep?
我睡觉时间很随意的
I sleep a lot, it varies.
昨天几点睡的？
What time did you get to sleep last night?
你睡了吗？
Did you get any sleep at all?
现在正是非常时期
These are busy times.
不需要我来提醒你
You don't need a doctor to tell you
你这样下去是慢性自杀吧
that you're working yourself into an early grave.
那么长时间…
The long hours...
你打电话过来
Okay, when you called me just now,
拨的是什么号？
what number did you dial?
你家里的号码
Your home number.
挂掉电话 煮上可可
Cell is off, cocoa is on the stove,
准备好枕边读物
book is at my bedside.
不出两小时我就会睡着了
I'll be asleep in under two hours.
谢谢你打电话来 医生
Thanks for calling, Doctor.
在共和党
In the Republican party,
他可以帮你在加州…
he can help you out in California...
好吧！
Okay!
太好了 欢迎
Good, welcome.
是啊
Yes! Yeah.
我想带你见见参议员戴维森
I want you to meet Senator Davidson.
我很感激 每次资金筹集活动你都来参加
Yes. I appreciate you coming to every fundraiser.
我马上回来
Yeah, I'll be right back.
你好 期待下次见面
Hello! I expect to see you next time.
那太好了
Yes. That would be great.
见到你很高兴
Yes, nice to see you.
打算休息了？
Early night?
如果是冲说辞来的 别耽误时间了
If you're looking for a quote, you're wasting your time.
我刚注意到
I've just watched you extricate yourself
每间隔三十分钟 你就脱身去洗手间一次
from three conversations
总共去了三次
to use the ladies' room in the space of 30 minutes.
被你发现了 我控制不住 你说的没错
You busted me. I'm incontinent. Write it up.
真希望我的判断是错的
I hope I'm wrong,
但你这样会使人误认为你厌倦了这个地方
but one might think you're sick of this town.
你是邮局的人吗？怎么入场的？
You from the Post? How did you get in?
我就想占用你五分钟的时间
I'd just like five minutes of your time.
好吧
Fine.
我走到停车场只要三分钟 开门见山吧
Walk to my car is three, get to the point.
我听国会的人说 反枪支管制协会的人
The word on the Hill is that the gun lobby
接近你 想要反枪支管制
approached you over Heaton-Harris
被你回绝了
and you refused.
我对“国会的人说”不评价
I don't comment on "word on the Hill."
我了解你这样做唯一的原因
I know the only way you'd do that
就是你支持这项法案
is if you support the bill.
这么说来就有趣了
That's quite a story.
拒绝掉一位重要的委托人
Turning down a prized client because
因为你无法接受他们的立场
you can't accept what they stand for.
但对于信念坚定的说客伊丽莎白·斯隆 谁知道呢
Elizabeth Sloane, the conviction lobbyist. Who knew?
请直奔主题
I said, get to the point.
你是否承认 目前的系统是不健全的
Will you admit the present system is broken?
我坚定地支持第二修正案
I remain committed to the Second Amendment.
在德州 假阳具是违法的
Dildos are illegal in Texas,
但民众却可以走进体育商店
but Joe Public can walk into a sports store
随随便便就买到猎枪
and walk out with a shotgun.
说明在德州
That would explain the low rate
用假阳具杀人还不多见
of dildo-related murders in Texas.
并不好笑
Okay, it wasn't that funny.
你想干嘛？
What do you want?
来一句说辞
Your quote.
好吧 一个笃定的说客
Fine. A conviction lobbyist
只相信靠自己能力取胜即可
need only believe in their ability to win.
真是至理箴言
That's a keeper.
还有件事 我们私下里说
One more thing, off the record.
- 嗯  - 你知道
- Mmm-hmm.  - What do you know about
- 反枪支管制协会的对手是谁吗？ - 是布拉迪运动那些人吗？
- the gun lobby's opponents?  - The Brady Campaign?
我知道他们会输 因为他们全部预算加起来
I know they're going to lose because their total budget
还不如一个枪支说客
is less than what the gun lobby pays
花在擦鞋上的钱多
to get their shoes shined.
那他们的说客彼得森·怀亚特呢？
What about their lobbyists, Peterson Wyatt?
他们是一个精密的两党联立政府事务机构
They're a boutique bipartisan Government Affairs agency.
“精密”就是委婉表达规模小
"Boutique" is a euphemism for "little fish."
“两党联立”就是一群嬉皮士在耍宝
"Bipartisan" denotes a bunch of hippies in suits.
你知道他们的首席执行官是谁吗？
Do you know anything about their CEO?
一个叫施密特的人
Guy named Schmidt?
没听说过
No, never heard of him.
但既然是公司老大
But if the firm is built in his image,
估计一定是个虚与委蛇
I'm sure he's a simpering wuss
外强中干的胆小鬼
with a Ph.D in style-over-substance.
好吧
Got it.
我还没有自我介绍呢
I never introduced myself, by the way.
我叫鲁道夫·施密特
My name's Rodolfo Schmidt,
彼得森·怀亚特的首席执行官
CEO of Peterson Wyatt.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
我还没有你想象中的那样虚与委蛇吗？
Am I not simpering hard enough?
你的公司成立十二年了
Your firm's 12 years old,
我还以为你会叫彼得森什么的…
I'd think your name would be Peterson or...
这…
What...
这是什么情况？
What is this about?
你是希顿·哈里斯的拥护者
You're pro-Heaton-Harris.
现在人尽皆知
It's an open secret
你和你的上司正对着干
you're at war with your firm's leadership.
布拉迪团队想要你
The Brady Campaign wants you
把争论引到法案通过上
to lead the fight to pass the bill.
你要为我们辩护
You'd run defense out of our office.
事成之后
When it's over,
白宫大人物随你挑
you can choose from any of the D.C. behemoths
都会排队要你的签名
lining up for your signature.
这就是彼得森·怀亚特公司邀请你加入的说辞
This is Peterson Wyatt's quote for your services.
不知道这算是称赞
I don't know if I should be flattered
还是侮辱 施密特先生
or insulted, Mr. Schmidt,
不过显然你搞错我的立场了
but you clearly have the wrong opinion of me.
我可不这么认为
I think my opinion of you is right on.
别告诉我你不想插一手
Don't tell me you don't want to take a swing at this.
再见 施密特先生
Goodbye, Mr. Schmidt.
你的车呢？
Where's your car?
应该在洗车行吧 我不自己开车
Should be at the valet by now. I don't drive.
[一个笃定的说客 是不能只相信靠能力取胜的]
喂 简
Hi, Jane?
我知道很晚了
Yeah, I know what time it is.
听着…
Listen...
如果苏格拉底什么都没写过
If, uh, Socrates never wrote anything,
那别人是怎么知道这个人的呢？
how is it anyone's ever heard of him?
我们需要开个会
Look, we need a meeting.
参议员雅各布斯安排住在什么地方？
Where are they putting Senator Jacobs?
龙目岛上的小旅馆吗？
The Lombok Lodge?
是的
Yes.
- 旅馆在沙滩上？ - 是的
- It's on the beach?  - Yes.
很好
Good.
这个上交给参议院道德委员会
This goes off to the Senate Ethics Committee.
一经批准
Once they authorize the travel,
我们就送他上飞机
Jacobs is on a plane.
- 这样可以吗？ - 没事的
- Is that okay?  - It's fine.
- 理论上讲真的可以吗？ - 不必担心
- Technically, I mean?  - Don't worry about it.
只是… 作为说客 我们是不可以
It's just... As lobbyists, we can't be involved
为国会成员安排海外旅行的
in arranging overseas travel for members of Congress.
我闲暇时间在道德法规上读到的
I read ethics regs when I want to look busy.
如果你好好读一下
If you weren't just pretending to be busy,
你就会发现这事情是有变通方法的
you'd know that the workaround
那就是找到一个非盈利组织
is to get this to the non-profit,
叫他们签好字 上报给道德委员会就好了
have them sign and file with the Ethics Committee.
我是不是管的有点多了？
Do I seem unduly concerned?
好的
Okay.
乔治给我说了桑福德的事
George told me what happened with Sandford.
- 嗯  - 你脑子坏了吗？
- Mmm.  - Are you retarded?
你早餐为什么要吃巧克力蛋糕？
Why are you eating a chocolate cake for breakfast?
- 你好意思吗？ - 这是松饼
- Have you no shame?  - It's a muffin.
你早餐没有吃过松饼吗？
You never had a muffin for breakfast?
原来是松饼啊
A muffin, let's see.
鸡蛋 牛奶 面粉 糖 可可粉 巧克力
Eggs, milk, flour, sugar, cocoa powder, chocolate.
听上去和蛋糕也没差 话说回来
That sounds exactly like a cake, but of course,
没什么正常人
no civilized person would ever eat
会把巧克力蛋糕当做早餐
a chocolate cake for breakfast.
你真是疯了
You've lost your mind.
富兰克林 你弄明白了吗？
Franklin, are you getting this?
我要问你了
'Cause I'm really talking to you.
嗯？
Huh?
磨茹白蛋糕并不是真正的蛋糕
Shmallow Cakes aren't really cakes.
而是巧克力涂层的
They're marshmallow paste sandwiched
棉花糖夹心饼干
between two cookies covered in chocolate.
既然蛋糕不在免税范围内
And while our tax code deems cakes
越发受到强烈征税
luxury items and hits them harder,
饼干的未来就变得明亮了
cookies are obviously necessities,
必然也会被免税
and therefore exempt.
- 你懂了吗？ - 懂什么？
- Are you getting this?  - What?
将磨茹白蛋糕重新定义为饼干
Have Shmallow Cakes re-designated as cookies,
这种文字游戏只是一种营销手段而已
argue cake in the name is merely marketing puff.
在庭上需要用证据说话
You'll need evidence in court,
利用专家的意见
but get a team of scientists to opine
说服别人这东西八成是饼干 并非什么蛋糕
that they are in fact 80% cookie and zero percent cake.
你就稳赢了
That's how you win.
这你都懂？
You knew that all along?
总有一天你也会懂的
You would have got there eventually.
你告诉我这些做什么呢？
Then why are you telling me this?
为了让你不跟我走
In case you're not coming with me.
这什么情况？
What's going on?
好了 各位
All right, everyone.
我请各位来 是要宣布
I called you here to announce that,
很快
effective immediately,
我要离开这里
I am leaving Cole Kravitz
去彼得森·怀亚特公司
and starting work as lead consultant
做布拉迪运动的首席顾问了
for the Brady Campaign at Peterson Wyatt.
我向在座的各位担保
I've secured positions for everyone in this room
去到那边 你们的薪酬不减
without change to your current compensation.
谁愿意跟我走？
So, who's with me on this?
我刚费了老大力气
I just spent the last hour wiping your shit
帮你收买下比尔·桑福德
off Bill Sandford's shoes,
和他保证 找到你
assuring him that you're the right lady
他就不用愁了！
to broaden his membership!
本来都离成功不远了！
We're inches from a green fucking light!
我猜你是带不走了
So, you're saying I should put you down as a maybe?
你毫无胜算的！
You can't possibly win this!
有人跟我走吗？
Who's with me?
我跟你走
I'm with you.
别激动 罗斯 我需要你
Whoa, whoa, Ross, hey, come on, I need you.
她更需要我
She needs me more.
亚历克斯？
Alex?
劳伦？
Lauren?
搞什么？你们当是在拍《甜心先生》吗？
The fuck is this? Jerry Maguire?
你看了《甜心先生》？
You've seen Jerry Maguire?
我不喜欢枪支
Guns frighten me.
还有谁要跟我走？
So, Sloane and Co. Versus Connors and who else?
奥海拉 维克曼 摩尔 上帝使团
Mmm. O'Hara, Wickman, Moore, the God Squad.
拉米雷斯
Ramirez,
你手里有几支枪了？
how many Tec-9s do you own again?
足够我保护自己的财产安全了
Enough to defend my property.
还留了两支用来对付左翼分子
Plus two more to piss off the lefties.
好了 简
All right, Jane,
联系彼得森怀亚特公司的鲁道夫·施密特
contact Rodolfo Schmidt at Peterson Wyatt,
告诉他们我们总共有六个人要过去
and tell him there's a total of six coming over.
我数是五个啊
I count five.
你数学真不咋地
Mathematician you are not.
谁说我要跟你走了？
Who said I was coming?
我说的 快给鲁道夫打电话
I did. Call Rodolfo.
我要是想留下来呢？
What if I'm staying?
老天 现在可不是
Jesus, now is not the time to develop
开玩笑的时候 简
a sense of humor, Jane.
我并没有开玩笑
That's good, 'cause I'm not.
没事 你去吧
Seriously, kid, go.
不用管我
I could care less.
之前你说的对
You were right before.
读研究生就是一种逃避
About post-grad. Maybe it is a cop-out.
我所在的公司是这个城市最好的
I'm at one of the best firms in the city.
你的名望可能可以支撑你
Your reputation might survive a move
投入到一项毫无成功希望的战斗
to some third-tier outfit to fight a losing battle.
但我不同
Mine won't.
有道理
No shit.
我收回刚才的话
I take it back.
过去的几年 我从你那学到不少 利兹
I've learned a lot from you these last couple years, Liz.
我会想念你
I'll miss you.
但你凌晨三点打给我的电话
The 3:00 a.m. wake-up calls?
却没什么好怀念的
Not so much.
显然 你学到的不只有这些
You've obviously learned more than you let on.
刚刚过去的一分钟你展现的雄心壮志
You've shown more ambition in the last 60 seconds
比过去两年投入到工作中的还要多
than I've seen in the prior two years,
你却痴心妄想
but you are delusional
没有我 你自己可以立足脚跟吗
if you think you can survive without me.
等我们再次针锋相对
If we butt heads on this,
我就不会那么让着你了
don't think I'll show you any compassion.
基于这点
And with that in mind,
我打算再给你一个重新考虑的机会
I will give you a final opportunity to reconsider.
好了 我要去和大金融家们告别了
All right. I'm off to say my goodbye to the money-man.
到时候你若是
When this town guts you like a trout
被现实抽筋剥肚
and chokes you with your own entrails,
可别来找我哭鼻子哦
don't come sniveling to me.
过会我们会
We'll come back
回到亚洲印度尼西亚共和国一案
to the Asian Republic of Indonesia later,
我所担心的
but, you see, what troubles me
是你呼风唤雨的影响力
is the amount of influence you had.
我们已经收到
We've seen communications
华盛顿很多高级人物的来信
from senior figures in Washington
他们都担心 你身为说客
who feared that you, a lobbyist,
弹指一挥 就可以轻松毁掉他们的饭碗
could destroy their careers with a snap of your fingers.
你给自己树立的
Is this reputation something
就是这样一个形象吗 斯隆女士？
you've cultivated, Miss Sloane?
鉴于法律顾问的建议
Upon the advice of counsel,
恕我无法回答你的问题
I must respectfully decline to answer your question,
根据美国宪法第五修正案
based on my rights under the Fifth Amendment
我有权保持沉默
to the United States Constitution.
作为个人
You see, it's bad enough one person
拥有如此巨大的影响力不是什么好事
having that much influence,
如果这种人身上
but if they're out of control, if she has a problem,
存在癖嗜的问题
an addiction, well,
就好比美国政舰
it would be like the ship of American politics
是由醉鬼掌舵一样
is being steered by a drunk.
你是否有过
Do you, or have you ever had,
药物滥用的情况？
any problems with substance abuse?
鉴于法律顾问的建议
Upon the advice of counsel,
恕我无法回答你的问题
I must respectfully decline to answer your question,
根据美国宪法第五修正案
based on my rights under the Fifth Amendment
我有权保持沉默
to the United States Constitution.
我了解你睡眠困难？
I understand you have difficulty sleeping?
我们传审了你的病历记录
We subpoenaed medical records.
你长期患有慢性失眠
You're a long-time sufferer from chronic insomnia.
每天工作超过十六小时
You regularly work over 16 hours a day.
但无法入睡 是这样的吧？
But you can't get off to sleep. ls this accurate?
鉴于法律顾问的建议 我无法…
Upon the advice of counsel, I respectfully...
恕我无法回答你的问题
I must respectfully decline to answer your question,
根据
based on my rights under
美国宪法第五修正案
the Fifth Amendment of the United States...
我有权保持沉默
To the Constitution.
随便吧
Whatever.
医生为你开具了
You were prescribed
多重苯二氮平类药物处方
multiple courses of benzodiazepines,
但根据一位
but according to the deposition
目击证人的证词
of one of our witnesses,
你一直都在通过某种手段 在无处方的情况下
you've been procuring, off-prescription,
购买精神振奋类药物
a course of psycho-stimulants,
目的就是要延长清醒时间
with the aim of keeping you awake a little longer.
这是真的吗？
Is this true?
斯隆女士？
Miss Sloane?
鉴于法律顾问的建议
Upon the advice of counsel,
恕我无法回答你的问题
I must respectfully decline to answer your question,
根据美国宪法第五修正案
based on my rights under the Fifth Amendment
我有权保持沉默
to the United States Constitution.
好吧 我们回到
Okay. Getting back to this business
亚洲印度尼西亚共和国一案
of the Asian Republic of Indonesia...
我没有滥用药物
I am not a drug addict,
这一连串的质疑与…
and this line of questioning has no revel...
与此案无关
Relevance in this case.
我所服用的药物对我判断力的影响
My medication doesn't affect my judgment
同双份特浓咖啡无二差
any more than a double espresso.
说到药物神经麻痹
And speaking of intoxication,
我可以清楚地背出
I can recite from memory
一票醉酒后参与立法投票的
a list of upstanding, elected Senators
所谓正直的参议员的名单
who voted on legislation while severely inebriated.
现在
And just so you know, I think, by now,
我们都清楚了
we are fully aware,
还有 千万不要忘记
and in no danger of forgetting,
印度尼西亚是个共和国
that Indonesia is a republic,
只是碰巧位于亚洲大陆而已
which happens to be situated on the continent of Asia.
斯隆女士
Miss Sloane.
欢迎加入
Welcome to the party.
五年了
Five years.
真的值吗？
Was it really worth it?
- 少说五年  - 什么五年？
- Five years minimum.  - What's five years?
都拿印尼在亚洲来强词夺理
All for some puerile quip about Indonesia being in Asia.
你难道看不出 他们这样就是为了…
Can't you see that whole construct was designed to...
还真奏效了
And it worked.
你能不能告诉我什么五年？
Are you gonna tell me what five years is?
你上当了
You fell for it.
国会山上最机警的人
The smartest operative on the Hill
却让辛普森爷爷耍了
Just got played by Grampa Simpson!
我们就不能
Is it how long this conversation's
说点别的吗？
gonna feel like?
这是在国会前用现行汇率作伪证
It's the going rate for perjury before Congress.
现在你又否决了第五修正案
Now you've thrown out the Fifth,
想搞垮你的人
anyone who wants you in the ground,
不是个小数目
and that's a lot of people, they're hard at work
他们整天没日没夜
dedicating their creative and intellectual efforts
目的就是抓住你说谎的把柄
to catching you in a lie.
如果我一直保持沉默呢？
Well, what if I just stay silent?
真是个好主意
Well, that's a great idea.
你的律师怎么没想到这点呢
Shit, why didn't your lawyer think of that?
如果我拒绝回答…
If I refuse to answer...
他们会以轻视国会的罪名
They'll throw you in jail
- 把你关进大牢！ - 小点声
- for contempt of Congress!  - Shh!
你给他们留下了一个大机会！
You've just blown this thing wide open!
冷静点 丹尼尔
Calm down, Daniel.
你现在的样子像是很关心一样
You're starting to look like you care.
不
No.
我不想关心你
I don't care about you
我更想丢下你不管
any further than I can throw you.
我为国会山进行道德游说
I work for the one ethical lobbying practice on the Hill,
结果还要为模范人物
and I wind up defending the poster child
既信仰疗法后
for the most morally bankrupt
最大的道德破产进行辩护
profession since faith healing.
你的车在楼下
Your car's downstairs.
回家等着被钉上十字架吧
Go home, stare at the ceiling, get ready to be crucified.
我知道自己没有很好地
I know I don't have the most stellar record
接受你的建议…
in heeding your advice...
别再发假誓了！
Don't perjure yourself!
在伊丽莎白那没有成功 真是太糟了
Too bad things didn't pan out with Elizabeth.
[十一周前]
我们还有其他选择
Oh, we have other options.
“阿米什鸡”是什么鬼东西？
What the hell is "Amish chicken"?
一种营销运动吗？
A marketing exercise?
我们正在找其他的说客
No, we'll just try and find ourselves another lobbyist.
我说的是阿米什鸡
I was talking about the Amish chicken.
哦
Oh.
她现在与你为敌
She's your enemy now.
我请你来 是因为
I invited you here because nobody
除了我们 没有人压制的了她
is better placed to neutralize her than us.
我们共事多年
We worked together for years.
非常清楚她的工作套路
We know exactly how she operates.
对了 阿米什鸡
Oh, that is just a regular bird
不过是阿米什地区饲养的一种鸟类
raised in Amish country, by the way.
啊
Ah.
因为信息封闭 所以吃起来更香是吗
It tastes better because it can't use Google, huh?
有超过五百万人同我们一样
Look, there's over five million of us.
拥有枪支
And we're armed.
我们曾否决过此类法案
We've beaten this kind of bill before,
这次也会成功
we'll beat it again.
民众会发起反抗
They'll make a lot of noise,
会表示不满 但最终
they'll wave their banners, but in the end
结果是可预知的
it's so predictable.
她是不可预知的
She's not predictable.
她的目的就是出其不意
She aims to surprise.
她会同自己的团队分享
She'll share things with her team,
但有所保留
but she won't share everything.
她会针对不同人制定计划
She'll have a plan for certain people,
但事后
but they won't know until they're dropped
他们才会意识到自己被利用
right into the middle of it.
她总是难以捉摸
There's always something else going on with her.
这就是她的工作方式
It's just how she works.
我们很清楚她会求助什么样的参议员
We have a good idea which Senators she'll go for
我们可以提前下手
and we can get in first.
对比其他人
And they're vulnerable on other members
他们要脆弱得多
they're already counting on.
密歇根的巴杰利
Badgley, Michigan.
手里掌握着六票之多
He can bring maybe six votes.
接近他 我们就很容易取胜了
We get to him, it's a quick win.
好吧
All right.
给我见识见识你们的间谍情报术吧
Show me some Badgley.
- 菲列牛排 一分熟  - 菲列牛排 要全熟
- Filet mignon, rare.  - Same, well done.
我也是
Well done too.
红点鲑
The Arctic char.
阿米什鸡肉沙拉 谢谢
Amish chicken salad, please.
失陪
Excuse me.
是你的洞察力帮你走到这一步
That kind of insight is exactly why you're here.
谁来过他这一关呢？
I'm sorry, who closed him again?
你谁啊？
Who the hell are you?
晚上好 女士
Evening, ma'am.
每次都来的那个马克呢？
What happened to the usual guy? Mark.
他是叫这个名字吧
If that's his real name.
马克不在这里了
Mark's moved on.
叫我福德就好
Call me Forde.
这是你的真实名字吗
Is that your real name?
是你的专属名字
Is to you.
- 你呢 可人？ - 天啊
- How about you, gorgeous?  - Oh, God.
你是政客 还是法人代表什么的？
You a politico, or one of these corporate-types?
你这样一位可人 怎么要到这里来呢？
What brings a fine lady like you to room 904?
不管你的事 你喝了多少？
Not the conversation. How much you had to drink?
毕竟这里随便喝 我喝得还不算多
Well, a free minibar, I'd say not nearly enough.
这里不能抽烟
You're not allowed to smoke in here.
这里也不能叫鸭
You're not allowed to buy company in here,
可你还是叫了
yet here you are.
抽烟是可以检测到的
Smoke is detectable.
会吸引别人的注意 你这样太不专业了
It could draw attention. It is unprofessional.
好吧
Okay.
真是一股政治气 你是律师吗
Corporate-type. Lawyer, maybe.
想继续的话
If we're going to proceed,
就得按照…
I require a certain standard of...
规矩办事
Agency rules, lady.
我只收现金
Payment in cash, I'm the only one
给钱我就不会告诉别人我们见过
to know this little party here ever happened.
也要为这些酒买单
And that's with half a minibar down my gullet.
你在找什么别的东西吧
I understand if you were looking for something else.
好吧
You'll do fine.
我们直奔主题吧
Let's get to the point.
好吧
All right.
但愿你们没有待在贫民窟里的感觉
Hey, I hope you guys don't feel like you're slumming.
我觉得还不如贫民窟呢
I thought it'd be weirder.
有坐垫有秋千
Bean bags, couple swings, maybe.
最起码也得有淋浴间吧
At least tell me you guys have shower rooms.
科尔·克拉维茨公司有淋浴间？
Cole Kravitz had shower rooms?
委托人同他待上三十分钟
Clients felt like they needed one
就会想去洗澡了
after 30 minutes with him.
我们设备齐全 只是没时间用
We had all the facilities, and no time to use them.
这样挺好的
This'll do fine.
楼下的自动贩卖机好怪
The vending machine downstairs is weird.
必须要知道性别和年龄范围
Wouldn't give me my beverage
才肯卖饮料出来
until I told it my gender and age range.
自动贩卖机公司
The vending machine company sells
把我们的个人资料卖给比格广告公司了
our personal details to Big Advertising.
我已经投诉他们了
I already posted a complaint.
没关系 我没提供真实信息
It's okay, I just lied.
你告诉它自己成年了？
You told it you were an adult male?
你为什么对他这么不友好？
Why are you so horrible to him?
雅各布斯刚搞定了能多益税
Jacobs just pulled the Nutella Tax.
- 什么时候的事？ - 我刚听说的
- When did that happen?  - I just got it.
棕榈油税？是你们搞定的？
The tax on palm oil? You're the ones who killed it?
像渡渡鸟一样都是过去的事了
Dead with the dodo.
印尼雨林里
Along with how many other unique species
其他的稀世物种也一样吗？
in the Indonesian rainforest?
你这个比方可真不咋地
Not your greatest analogy there.
这就看他们了
I guess it should be up to them,
毕竟国家是人家自己的
I mean, it is, after all, their country.
你知道他们那种原始的刀耕火种法
Do you know how much pollution their slashing and burning
给大气层带来多少污染吗？
pumps into the atmosphere?
占不到温室效应排放量的百分之零点二
Less than 0.2% of global greenhouse emissions.
- 这些谣言都是真的咯？ - 是的
- So, are the rumors true?  - Yes.
罗斯真是个娘娘腔
Ross is really a woman.
斯隆是艾斯·库伯的翻版吧？
Is Sloane the personification of an ice cube?
她平时都是站着尿尿
She pees standing up.
我都不那么尿尿
And, like... I don't even do that.
你讲话经大脑吗？
Do you think before you speak?
- 早上好  - 早
- Good morning.  - Good morning.
- 早  - 早
- Morning.  - Morning.
这样吧 我们按座位顺序
I was thinking, perhaps, we go around the table,
挨个介绍一下自己
introduce ourselves.
我们来点有趣的吧
Let's spare ourselves the tedium.
想要打破僵局吗 拿出你的洞察力来吧
If you want to break the ice, do it with insight.
我们坐在这里 都是为了推动
We're all here to ensure safe passage
希顿·哈里斯反枪支法案顺利收入联邦法律
of the Heaton-Harris Bill into Federal law.
我们该怎么做呢？
How do we do it?
事实上 我们做不到
Realistically, we don't.
我们能做的 只是尽自己所能
We fight as hard as we can,
建立强大的支持基础
build a strong base of support,
这样才能增大明年
so we have a better chance
讨论希顿·哈里斯法案时的胜算
when they introduce next year's Heaton-Harris,
或者后年
or the one after that.
我来这里
I didn't just move across town
可不是为了放慢失败的脚步的
with the aim of losing as slowly as possible.
你的名字和工龄？
Name and seniority?
埃斯米·曼尼克瑞安 工龄九年
Esme Manucharian, nine years.
曼尼克瑞安 我听说过你
Manucharian, I've heard that name.
埃斯米是我们请来的控枪专家
Esme's our authority on gun control.
只要有准确的资料
When it comes to facts and figures,
她无人能及
she has no equal.
是你领导了保护
You led the fight to preserve
伊利诺伊州隐藏禁令的斗争
the concealed carry ban in Illinois.
最后失败了 是我做的
Ultimately unsuccessfully, but, yes.
埃斯米 为什么会失败呢？
Okay, Esme. Why are we going to lose?
你知道布拉迪每在运动上投入一美元
For every dollar Brady spends on campaign contributions,
反枪支说客要投入多少吗？
you know how much the gun lobby spends?
- 三十八美元  - 三十八美元
- Thirty-eight.  - Thirty-eight.
政客毁于金钱 但这是为什么呢？
So, politicians bow to money. But, why?
钱又不揣进他们兜里 那样的话就是贿赂了
It's not going into their pocket, that'd be bribery.
就像印尼方对参议员雅各布斯所做的那样吗？
Like what the Indonesians just did to Senator Jacobs?
这是基于教育目的
That was legal bribery
的合法化的贿路 但也是贿赂
for educational purposes. But, yes.
参议员的优先权不在于代表群众
A senator's priority isn't representing the people,
而在于足不出户
it's keeping his ass in office.
真是嘲讽啊
That is so cynical.
“嘲讽”是乐观主义者
"Cynical" is a word used by Pollyannas
用来表达对童真的缺乏的
to denote an absence of the naivety
这表达真是强烈啊
they so keenly exhibit.
你融入得还真是快
Wow. You settle in fast.
如果参议员只在乎保全自己的职位
If senators only care about protecting their position,
不就成为了公众舆论的奴隶？
wouldn't that make them slaves to public opinion?
投票数据表明 多数美国人
Polling data puts a majority of Americans
都支持希顿·哈里斯反枪支
in favor of Heaton-Harris.
所以你们才会一输再输
And that's exactly why you keep losing.
实际上这是我们第一次接触枪支问题
Well, this is actually our first crack at guns,
但我接受你的观点
but I take your point.
什么观点？
What point?
我们太看重群众典论了
Public opinion is overrated.
参议员的中途改选率是百分之八十二
Midterm re-election rates for senators was 82%.
投票数是三十六
Voter turnout was 36.
我猜 其中大多数
And I'll bet most of them were
都是反枪支管制协会收买来的
paid-up members of the gun lobby.
多谢
Thank you.
我们的对手买通了
Our opposition has created a base of voters,
大量且狂热的选民
vast and fanatical,
这些人
who go out and vote exclusively
只对枪支问题进行投票
on the issue of guns.
我们该怎么对付这个状况？
How do we compete with that?
我们也培养自己的支持者
We build our own base of supporters,
只接受那些有意愿
who demonstrate a willingness
投枪支反对票的人
to get their asses into booths and vote against guns.
选民的意图受什么因素影响最大？
What's the best indicator of voter intention?
- 金钱！ - 财政！
- Money!  - Finance!
这就是我们的第一步
That's our first prong.
在群众阶层
Grassroots action
直截了当地发起捐赠
aimed squarely at soliciting donations.
不是空虚的名头 也不依赖网络的点击
Not names on a petition, not clicks in cyberspace.
他们会知道我们捐赠了多少钱吗？
Will they know how much we're raising?
非营利组织会对自己的财政情况作出报告
Non-profits have to report on their finances.
国会的每一位工作人员
And every Congressional staffer
都会盯着这些数据看
watches filing day like a hawk.
你们在外奔走之时
While you're out there hustling,
我去拜访那些有影响力
I'll be working influential senators
能够帮忙拉来同事的选票的参议员
who can deliver their colleagues' votes.
这是第二步
That's our second prong.
第三步 就是去搞清
Our third is to identify
是谁在支配我们的目标人群
who holds sway in target states.
那些雇员和工人阶级
Employers, workers' groups.
不能盲目闯入参议员办公室
Don't just waltz into a senator's office
就开始讲大道理
and make your case.
调查出他们信任的
Find out who they trust,
和不敢迁怒的对象
who they can't afford to piss off.
就说是这些人叫你来谈判的
Convince that person to make your case.
这样我们才能取胜
That is how we win.
不会开车？
Not a driver?
会 但是不开
I can, but I don't.
那你比我强 我都没拿到驾照
Well, you got further than me, I don't even have a license.
我的银行账户和自由主义者的良知
My bank account and liberal conscience
不允许我买车
won't justify my own car.
你是什么原因？
What's your excuse?
说实话 我车技可差了
To be honest, I suck at it.
十六岁的时候去考驾照
I took my test when I was 16.
结果这是我唯一一项没有通过的考试
Only exam I ever failed.
教练说我很鲁莽
My instructor told me I was reckless,
注意力也不集中
I lacked due care and attention.
从那以后我就知道自己有做政客的天赋了
Knew then and there I had a career in politics.
你条理很清晰
You weren't messing around in there.
是不是认识什么
Did you know someone?
枪支暴力的受害者
Someone who was a victim of gun violence.
不认识 为什么每个人都要问我一遍？
No, why does everyone assume that?
可能是因为你的观点很强硬吧
Strong opinions, maybe?
说得就好像只有亲身经历
As if I can only see the merits of an argument
才能看出是非曲直一样
when I feel the effects personally.
我曾认识一个国会议员 记不清名字了
There was a Congressman, I don't remember his name,
他的整个政治生涯都在反同性恋法
his whole career he was against gay rights,
直到他自己的哥哥出柜了才改变看法
only to do a complete U-turn when his brother came out.
多么有说服力的例子
What a well-reasoned basis for an opinion.
给他个小木槌 叫他去做法官
Give him a gavel, put him in a courthouse.
你饿了吗？
Are you hungry?
你每天晚上都来这里吃饭？
You eat here every night?
差不多 这地方基本不关门
Pretty much. Place never closes.
你怎么会不感到厌倦呢
How do you not get bored of it?
吃饭是必需行为啊
It's a necessity.
就好比我怎么能厌倦上厕所呢
It's like asking if I get bored of going to the toilet.
这么说来你可能觉得奇怪
Okay, this is going to sound alien to you,
但在我心里 食物占据了无与伦比的地位
but food takes up an inordinate amount of space in my head.
那枪支呢？
How about guns?
我尽职调查的时候 发现你的简历很突出
In doing my due diligence, your résumé stood out.
我注意到 你的很多工作都与轻武器相关
I noticed a lot of your work pertains to firearms.
我猜 是你有这样的思想偏好
I'm guessing that was a conscious decision
才会总做类似的工作吧
to steer things in that direction.
对这个问题 我的态度很强硬
It's an issue I feel strongly about.
这不关我的事
It's none of my business,
但我发现你的资料有缺口
but there was a gap in your profile.
九十年代后期 在去伯克利之前
Before Berkeley, you attended high school
你在印第安纳州布鲁明顿就读高中
in Bloomington, Indiana, in the late '90s.
但没有提到高中的名字
The name of the school isn't listed.
还有谁知道这件事？
Who else knows about this?
只有鲁道夫了
Rodolfo. That's all.
你应该猜得到我在想什么
You can imagine what I'm thinking.
打断一下 伊丽莎白 我的名誉是靠自己赚来的
I'm sorry, Elizabeth, but I earned my reputation.
与我在高中时发生的事
It didn't come from something
没有关系
that happened when I was in high school.
虽然我的观点受到了影响
Even if my views did.
公开发表意见甚至会减弱我的立场
Going public could even weaken my standing.
大家都评价我太情绪化
They'll say I'm too emotional.
不管怎样 真正用枪的人甚至都不会买枪
Anyway, the shooters didn't even buy their guns.
希顿·哈里斯
Heaton-Harris wouldn't have made
丝毫都不会在意
a shred of difference that day.
你担心立场薄弱…
You fear a weakened standing...
会毁掉你影响改变的能力
will damage your ability to effect change.
但如果一旦承认
But if acknowledging it was the difference
就会面临大输大赢的落差呢？
between winning and losing?
如果你放过我 把我和其他人同等对待
I'd appreciate it if you just treated me
我会很感激你的
as one of the team.
我能看出来你很有工作能力
A highly competent one, I can tell.
有你这样的员工是我们的幸运
We're lucky to have you.
六十是个神奇的数字
Sixty is the magic number.
只要六十票 就可以阻碍议案通过
Sixty votes breaks a filibuster.
反枪支管制协会四十一票通过？
So, the gun lobby wins with 41?
他们不需要这么多票也能通过
They could win with fewer.
我们需要达到六十票 少一票都不行
We need to hit 60. Anything less doesn't cut it.
五十九票都不行
Fifty-nine doesn't cut it.
我们需要找六十位参议员投票
We need 60 senators to show up and vote.
如果找不到 那就是看着他们胜利
We don't get that, they win, period.
正如我所说…
As I was saying...
我认为 反枪支管制协会
That by my reckoning, the gun lobby
能稳拿三十四票
has 34 votes pretty much locked.
就是这边这些人
And that's this side.
我们稳拿四十四票 就是这些人
I'd say we have 44 locked over here on this side.
还剩二十二人
That leaves 22 that are still in play.
就是中间这些人
These fine ladies and gentlemen in the middle.
希顿·哈里斯
Heaton-Harris, provisionally,
是在八十四天内临时赶超的
makes it to the floor in 84 days.
好消息是
The good news is,
只要再搞定十六人 我们就达标了
if we can lock 16, we're over the line.
这算是好消息？
I'm sorry, that's the good news?
二十二人里面搞定十六人？
We need 16 out of 22 votes?
这就好比考试及格线
That's like sitting an exam where the passing grade is...
是七十二分一样
72% .
那坏消息是 游说议员反对管制枪支买卖的人
And the bad news is that the gun lobby
比我们想象中要有钱得多？
is rich beyond our wildest dreams?
这是一点
There is that.
还有要想从华盛顿
Or that it's not a whole lot of time
最具势力的人手中得到十六票 我们的时间已所剩无几了？
to steal 16 votes from the most powerful group in D.C.?
这也是
That, too.
罗斯想说的重点是 我们需要十六票
What Ross is fumbling for is, we need 16.
他们只需要七票
They only need seven.
该死
Shit.
…而整件事的始作俑者
and the man who did this
却在我们的伤口上撒盐
robbed us of their smiles, of their laughter.
我真的不能接受这种事情的发生
And I just can't accept that we allowed it to happen.
我们可爱的女儿 我们本可以避免这样的事情
Our beautiful girls, and we could have stopped it.
我们本可以卸掉他的枪
We could have taken the gun
这样我们的宝贝就…
out of his hand and my babies...
天啊
Jesus Christ.
就放到这里吧
We get the idea.
布伦达和乔尔·帕特森
Brenda and Joel Patterson.
枪击案在维斯康星
The shooting sparked a new wave
掀起了新一轮的反枪支热潮
of anti-gun sentiment in Wisconsin.
但那已经是一个月前的事了
And that was more than a month ago.
但事件的热度并没有衰退
It's not dying down.
布伦达已经成为“母亲需求运动”中
Brenda's become a prominent figure
非常具有代表性的一员
in the Mothers Demand Action movement.
每发生一起枪击案 公众的愤怒
Public outrage after a gun attack
都会持续大约一个星期的时间
lasts maybe a week per casualty.
公众现在对于帕廷森事件 应该已经不再关注了
This whole Pattinson story should be in the ground by now.
- 是帕特森  - 什么？
- Patterson.  - Huh?
他们的名字 是叫帕特森
Their name. The Patterson family.
我他妈才不管他们叫什么名字
I don't give a shit if they're the fucking Partridge Family.
那不是重点
This is her.
得有人告诉桑德福
Sandford needs to know.
我们的说辞必须具有很强的说服性
Our delivery must be tailored for maximum impact.
过去的两周里 枪支管制的支持率已经提升了百分之八
Support for gun control is up 8% in the last two weeks.
威斯康星的议员都很受挫
Both Wisconsin senators are vulnerable.
如果他们不支持希顿·哈里斯
If they don't declare for Heaton-Harris,
柯克帕特里克就撑不过今年秋天
Kirkpatrick won't make it through the fall,
华莱士在两年内也会被推翻…
and Wallace is toast in two years...
医疗方面的事是谁负责的？
Who's going to that medical thing?
华莱士议员
Senator Wallace.
他可以说服另两个温和派的人
He can deliver two other moderates.
她是个天生的说客
And sure as she was born screaming,
她一定会抓住机会 收买他们的
she'll see that as her chance to box them in.
卡洛斯 这绝对不行
No, Carlos, that's unacceptable.
媒体必须到场 这才是最重要的环节
The media has to be there, that's the whole point.
必须要全方位的曝光 给他们施加压力
It has to be digitally stored and ready to be trotted out
让他没有打退堂鼓的机会
should he even think about backing down.
我马上发一张克拉拉·汤姆森的照片给你
I'm gonna send you a photo of Clara Thomson.
她坐在左前方 穿着…
She'll be front-left, wearing a...
克拉拉 你今天穿的什么？
Clara, what are you wearing?
黑色单肩连衣裙
One-shoulder black crepe dress.
一件黑色单肩连衣裙
A one-shoulder black crepe dress.
如果我们运气好 办公室里只会有她一个人
If we're lucky, it'll be the only one in the room.
谢谢你 卡洛斯
Thanks, Carlos.
艾利克斯 快告诉我一个医生
Hey, Alex, tell me it's feasible that a doctor
根本没时间参加 社交媒体之类的东西
wouldn't have time for all this social media bullshit.
如果是十五个小时的活儿 那肯定的
Yeah, if you're pulling 15-hour shifts, I guess.
太好了
Great.
[医缘网(Doximity)：全美最大的医生网络社区]
但或许他会对医缘网感兴趣
But he'd be on Doximity probably.
[医缘网(Doximity)：全美最大的医生网络社区]
领英网的医生版
The Medical version of Linkedln.
你就不能在我说了“太好了”之后就打住吗？
Could you not have just stopped when I said "great"?
早上好
Good morning.
还有时间看书？
Light reading?
你知道肺学是什么意思吗？
Do you even know what Doximity is?
我知道
Yes, I do.
研究肺的学问
It's the study of Doximity.
肺是不对称的 右边有三个肺叶 而左边只有两个
Lungs are asymmetrical. Right has three lobes, left two.
知道为什么吗？
You know why?
因为你的心脏需要位置？
Your heart needs the real estate?
非常好
Bravo.
所有人 集合！
All right, everybody, listen up!
对你而言 对不对称都不重要吧
Not a problem for you, I should imagine.
他们都有什么论点？都过来！模拟演习一下
What have they got? Come on! Arguments and rebuttals.
开始吧 振作精神！
Let's have it, wake up!
这是实现全国枪支实名制的第一步
It's the first step toward a national register of firearms.
散布恐慌
Scare mongering.
不会有人该这么说的
No one's even come close to proposing that.
如果真有人这么冲
And if they did,
他就出不了国会大厦了 下一个
it would have its own day in Congress. Next.
离充公也会越来越远
And it's two steps away from confiscation.
反对枪支管制的人 他们的虚假言论都是围绕
The gun lobby's rhetoric is based on the falsehood
我们要剥夺公众的权益来展开的 但这不是我们的本意
that we want to take something away from people. We don't.
我们只是想让那些坏人
We want to make it more difficult
获取枪支的途径更困难
for dangerous people to buy firearms.
如果我们连这种言论都推翻不了
If we can't burst this fallacy,
那干脆回家洗洗睡得了
we may as well go home.
埃斯米 把温迪·福尼斯的个人信息给我
Esme, get me a bio on Wendy Furniss, please?
- 好的  - 哈伍德·诺顿的执行总裁？
- Sure.  - Harwood Norton's CEO?
没错 她是弗吉尼亚第二有权势的老板
Mmm-hmm. Second largest employer in Virginia.
有两个议员都很摇摆不定
Both senators are teetering,
但如果我能拜托她去说服他们…
but if I can get her to reach out to them...
你不觉得让一个
You don't see the irony
国防承包商的执行总裁支持禁枪
in asking the CEO of a defense contractor
很荒唐吗？
to advocate for a ban on guns?
我们不是要禁枪！
We're not banning anything!
天啊 你说话的样子跟那帮人一模一样
Jesus, you sound like one of them.
我只是很投入
I'm in character.
下一个！
Next!
新规定会让等待时间
Uh, the new rules will increase
增加两星期
wait times by two weeks.
欢迎来到美国
Welcome to America,
你想照个X光 要等六个月
where you'll wait six months for an X-ray,
但如果你想买支AR-15步枪
but, hey, you can buy an AR-15
只需要十五分钟
in five minutes flat.
在公众面前 你要说得这么随性？
You going to be that flippant in public?
谨言慎行毫无记忆点 必须要一针见血
Pussyfooting isn't memorable. Sound bites are.
措辞合理的版本是这样的
And the appropriate one goes like this,
不能让极度渴望想要买枪的人
anyone that desperate to get their hands on a gun
这么容易地得到它
shouldn't be allowed anywhere near one.
威斯康星总共的核磁共振机器的数量…
The total number of MRI machines in Wisconsin...
[威斯康星州 密尔沃基]
这个议员一旦结束演讲
If the good Senator ever finishes this speech,
[威斯康星州 密尔沃基]
就会回答下面听众的问题
he will open it to the floor.
你排在第三个
You'll be question number three.
你觉得他会回答吗？
You think he'll go for it?
他知道媒体都在现场
He knows the media is here,
不会冒险在自己的资金凑集晚会上出丑的
won't risk being heckled at his own fundraiser.
一直逼问他 让他别无选择
Back him into a corner, and he'll have no choice.
…在我接下来的任期间
Of an additional $2 million
会在一年内启用额外的两百万
for the purchase of four brand-new machines
购买四台全新的机器
within the first year of my next term.
谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢 谢谢大家
Thank you very much. Thank you.
好了 再给大家几个机会
AH right, a few more questions
向议员提问 之后本次活动就结束了
for the Senator, then we'll wrap up.
好的 穿白衣服的女士
Uh, yes, the lady in white.
议员先生 我是韦斯特菲尔中心的主席…
Mr. Senator, I'm Chair of the Westfield Center...
第三个他应该叫我的 他在干什么？
He was supposed to go to me third, what's he doing?
准守命令
Following orders.
向后数三个桌子 向右两个
Three tables behind you, two to the right.
他们从威斯康星一直跟踪我们
They've been tracking us through Wisconsin.
可能名单上的人 他们都做了审查
They would have had everyone on that list vetted.
你被发现了
You're blown.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
也就是说 该启用备用方案了
I mean that it's time for plan B.
最后一个问题 拉杰·阿玛拉斯卡拉医生
And our final question goes to Dr. Raj Amarasekara.
希望我没有读错
I hope I'm pronouncing that right.
来自美国肺学协会
Of the Pulmonary Associates of America.
谢谢
Thank you.
拉杰·阿玛拉斯卡拉 实际上是一个名叫
Raj Amarasekara is a working actor
马修·坎塔利亚的演员
named Matthew Kantaria.
他们以为他会提关于
They think he's about to ask a benign question
清洁空气倡议的问题
about the clean air initiative.
…不难想象 我们会遇到三到四起枪击案
It's a safe bet we'll see three or four gunshot victims.
有些受害者还是孩子 年轻人
Some are kids, teenagers.
你为什么要在国会还没通过前 就想率先
How do you intend to vote on the Heaton-Harris Bill
支持希顿·哈里斯法案？
when it's put before Congress?
嗯…
Well...
正如你所说
As you have experienced, uh,
枪支暴力确实是真实存在的问题…
gun violence is a real problem...
你把我当诱饵？
You decoyed me?
拉杰·阿玛拉斯卡拉抄袭了
Raj Amarasekara has personally plagiarized
七篇研究论文 都可以在网上找到
seven research papers, all available online.
他还有医缘网的账号
He even has a Doximity account.
…财政负担确实是有的
Financial burden is the fact that
而有些受害者他们还是…
some of the victims are the, um...
小孩
Kids.
年轻人
The young.
所以我觉得 首要的是
So, I think it's, uh, first and foremost,
向那些受害者家属表示同情和慰问
to put our sympathies with the families of these victims.
但是的确 枪支暴力对于我们的医疗系统
But it's true, gun violence puts an enormous strain
以及其所需的人手 产生了很严重的负担
on our healthcare system and its work force.
确实是这样的
Absolutely, yes.
所以我才会全心全意支持
That's why I intend to give my whole-hearted support
希顿·哈里斯法案
to the Heaton-Harris Bill.
这叫掩人耳目
And that's a wrap.
谢谢大家 非常感谢
Thank you. Absolutely, thank you.
他还带了什么人？
Who else does he bring?
法希特利和加西亚
Fascitelli and Garcia.
埃斯米 星期三我给你准备了一个惊喜
Hey, Esme, I have a surprise for you on Wednesday.
去新餐厅吃饭？
We're going to a new restaurant?
参加纽约大学法学院 关于第二修正案的辩论如何？
How about a Second Amendment debate at NYU Law School?
别兴奋过头了
Don't shout this from the rooftops,
我相信你是整个团队
but I trust you to do a better job
最有实力的人
than anyone else on the team.
你不能去？
You can't make it?
刚刚说的整个团队里 也包括我自己
I'm including myself as part of the team.
我自己都还像个大学生
I wasn't cool enough to relate
要怎么给其他大学生演示
to college kids when I was a college kid.
稍后我会把细节发给你
I'll forward you the details.
又是你
You again.
我还专门打过电话 指名道姓叫他们派马克来
I called them and I specifically asked for Mark.
那我也专门告诉你 他跑路了
And I specifically told you he skipped town.
他去哪个代理公司了？
Well, what agency did he move to?
我怎么知道
How should I know?
我又不是他的保释官
I ain't his parole officer.
他碰到麻烦了？
He's in trouble?
我开玩笑的
I was kidding.
啊 我们那晚玩得多开心啊
Aww, we had so much fun the other night.
小姐 你知道门在哪儿
Well, you know where the door is, lady.
去找你的马克吧
Go run to your Mark.
我今晚有工作要忙
I've got work to do tonight.
大案子？
Big case?
福德 人机互动讲究的是互换原则
Forde, human interaction is an exchange.
我的钱交换你的…
My money for your...
老二？
Dick?
我想说的是“专项技能”
I was gonna say "skill set."
但这是我唯一愿意做的交换
But that's the only exchange I'm willing to make.
你现在听起来像个银行家一样
Now you sound like a banker.
我也得回去做准备了
I got to do prep anyways-
做什么准备？
For what?
明晚还有另一个客户
Another client, tomorrow night.
你还要做准备？
You do prep?
这是我的职责
For functions.
信不信由你
Believe it or not,
不是每个人雇我来 都是为了我的专项技能
not everyone hires me for my skill set.
有一半的客户 都只是想让我躺在她们怀中
Half my clients just want me on their arm.
有些人只是想找其他地方来的人
Some just want someone to talk to
诉诉苦 吐露一下心声
from a different neck of the woods,
- 反正也没人管得着  - 真是太可悲了
- who ain't gonna judge them.  - That is so pathetic.
所以职责也是不同的
Functions are different.
代理公司给了我一张身份清单
The agency gave me a list of covers.
保险主管 销售
Insurance exec, marketing guy.
明天扮演的角色是石油天然气工人
Tomorrow is oil and gas.
下次见
I'll be seeing you.
你还欠我点东西
I think you owe me something more.
都在里面了 你自己数
No, it's all there. Count it.
这钱是付我服务的
This covers my services.
但刚刚我跟你 分享了一大堆
But I just gave you a whole lot of information
关于我工作的细节
about my line of work.
根据我们的互换原则…
On your principles of exchange...
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
你刚刚是自愿跟我分享的
Okay, that was a voluntary donation on your part.
我付钱请你 是想体验一下
I pay you so I can imagine a life I chose
我为了追求事业 而选择放弃的那一种生活
to forego in the pursuit of my career.
那你为什么不退出？
So, why don't you go out and get it?
那不适合我
It's not for me.
至少在我还二十几岁时
Not when I was in my early 20s,
我不想过那样的生活
and sure as hell not now.
也就是“没有家”
So, "no house you call home,
“没有家人”
"no folks you call family,"
- 那样的生活？ - 没错
- sort of thing, huh?  - Uh-uh.
- 你有后悔过吗？ - 完全没有
- You ever regret that?  - Not for a second.
至少现在我们对彼此有了些许了解了
At least now we're peeling a layer.
我的互换原则就允许我透露这么多了
And that is all my principles of exchange will allow.
再见 福德
Goodbye, Forde.
如果你是个恐怖分子
If you're a terrorist,
或者某个不应该出现在那架飞机上的人
or someone who shouldn't be allowed on that plane,
你打算坐哪班航线？
which lane are you going to walk through?
没错 很显然…
Yeah, well, obviously...
星期四早上
Thursday morning.
好的 我会空出时间的
Okay, I'll hold.
- 劳伦！波士顿 星期四！ - 知道了！
- Lauren! Boston, Thursday!  - Got it!
我把自己所有的网上信息都删除了的
I deleted every vestige of my online existence.
但你没有替换它
You didn't replace it,
谷歌上找不到克拉拉这个人
leaving a Clara-sized hole in Google,
所以他们会做全面清查
which they flagged in due diligence.
我替换了的
I did replace it.
埃斯米！
Esme!
克拉拉·汤姆森做了两年无国界医生
Clara Thomson just returned from a 2-year stint
刚刚回国 这是千真万确的
with Médecins Sans Frontiéres. It was solid.
你为什么不告诉拉杰的事…
Why didn't you tell me about Raj...
叫他马修就好
Just call him Matthew.
我跟财政部的人核实过了
I checked with Finance.
你请的演员并没有用公司的钱
Your actor wasn't paid from our account.
你是自己掏钱请的他
You ran him out of your own pocket.
别把太多事情告诉身边的人 这是实战经验
It's good practice to keep your circle small.
在这个圈子里 不管你身在何处
In this town, no matter where you are,
可能在你周围不到两米的地方 就有一个叛徒
you're never more than two feet away from a rat.
嘿！美国火箭协会晚宴上的发言交给你了
Hey! I want you on the podium at the ARS dinner.
等等 这件事很重要啊
Wait, that's a huge deal.
你不觉得我们该分享一下
You don't think we should share
公众演讲的机会吗？
the public speaking a little?
然后把你好不容易积累下来的名声都败掉？
And blow all the goodwill you've racked up?
面对聚光灯我可能会不适应
I'm not sure I'm comfortable in the spotlight.
还要回答各种媒体的提问
Doing all the press.
那就给我适应起来 就这么说定了
Get comfortable, that ship has sailed.
好的 星期四早上 我会去的
Hey, yes. Thursday morning, I'll be there.
每天 都有四十八个小孩或青少年死于枪杀
Every day, 48 children or teens are shot.
这还不是全世界范围的数据
That's not across the world, folks,
仅仅在美国就有这么多受害者
that's right here in America.
[新泽西州 爱迪生市]
我们请来一位嘉宾是来自
We are joined right now by a representative
[新泽西州 爱迪生市]
布雷迪运动的代表
from the Brady Campaign,
- 埃斯米·曼楚瑞安  - 是曼尼克瑞安
- Esme Manchurian.  - It's Manucharian.
[马萨诸塞州 新贝德福德]
居然自己找上门来了？
Knocking on doors, making house calls?
[马萨诸塞州 新贝德福德]
你花了多长时间 才找到这个地方？
How long did it take you to even get to this place?
这足以证明我有多希望
Consider it a sign of how important
你能加入我们了吧
it is that we get you on board.
为什么？
Why?
在你这么长一段卓著的职业生涯中
In your long and distinguished career,
你对女权一点贡献都没有
you've done precisely jack-shit for feminism.
因为我对性别不感兴趣
Because gender doesn't interest me.
你就差一个老二了
The only thing you're missing is a dick.
如果你能出庭的话
I think your presence in the room
[密歇根州 安阿伯市]
将会帮助我们
would be a great help
[密歇根州 安阿伯市]
得到霍夫兰德议员的支持
as I make our case to Senator Hofland.
上帝保佑 我们可以保护
God willing, we can help protect
自己身边的人 免受美国所经历的悲剧…
our neighbors from the kind of tragedy America has endured...
埃斯米… 曼楚瑞安
Esme... Manchurian.
曼尼克瑞安
Manucharian.
[新罕布什尔 汉诺威市]
在这个国家 每周都有五个女人
In this country, nine women are shot
被自己最亲密的伴侣枪杀
and killed by their intimate partners every week.
自杀率上升了五倍…
The risk of homicide goes up 500%...
跟我说这些数据没用 我又不是他妈的记者
Don't hurl stats at me, I'm not a fucking journalist.
你以为我不知道这些事？
You think I don't know all this?
那你愿意加入吗？
Does your membership?
因为现在是把这些事说透的最佳时机
Because now would be a great time to tell them.
拉尔森和帕尔已经
Larsson and Parr have donated
捐赠了数百万了
millions of their personal fortunes.
- 我知道  - 我不能再恳求更多了
- Yeah.  - I can't go hat-in-hand for more.
嘿 曼尼克瑞安！
Hey, Manchurian!
曼德尔遇到瓶颈了 我需要交流话题
Mandel's on the brink, I need conversational topics.
- 什么意思？ - 寒暄小叙
- What do you mean?  - Small talk.
就是毫无目的地随意闲聊
Idle nonsense of no import to anything.
你把自己的社交互动外包了？
You outsource your social interactions?
是啊 兴趣 爱好 还有… 孩子！
Yeah. Interests, hobbies... Kids!
要想讨好一个为人父母的人
There's no better way to butter up a parent
没有什么比夸赞他们的孩子 更容易的了
than to tell him how hot his kids are.
我这就去办
On it.
上次我们见面的时候 你最小的孩子
The last time we met, your youngest was
马上就要上常青藤了
knocking on the door of the Ivy League.
- 没错  - 他叫洛根 对吧？
- Yes.  - Logan, was it?
天啊！我都记不得我跟你讲过这件事了
Christ! I can't even remember that conversation.
来自美国护士协会的曼蒂·哈姆林
Mandy Hamlyn from the American Nurses Association
- 在三号线上！ - 啊！
- on line three!  - Ah!
国会有很多人对于你们
I think there are a great many on the Hill
慷慨的赞助都深表敬意
who have become so accustomed to your generous support,
给他们来点刺激的惊喜 未尝不是一件好事
it wouldn't hurt to give them a short, sharp shock.
不要让你的捐赠人多投钱 让他们少捐点
Your donors, don't ask for more. Ask for less.
如果你们真的很支持希顿·哈里斯
If you feel strongly about Heaton-Harris,
你们甚至可以提出
you could do worse
如若有任何议员不支持
than to pledge to cut ties to any senator
则取消与他的合作
who doesn't come out in favor.
也就是说 我们既能推波助澜
So, what, we're turning the screw,
同时又能省钱？
and saving money at the same time?
我不愿待在一个每周都会发生
I don't want to live in a society where there
校园枪击案的社会！
is a new school shooting every week!
所以一旦开始投票
That is why when put to vote,
我一定会毫无保留地支持希顿·哈里斯法案！
I will be supporting the Heaton-Harris Bill!
是匿名捐赠的
It came in anonymously,
但所有人都认为捐赠人是彭博
but everyone's thinking Bloomberg.
五十万美元？这比我们的预算都还要高百分之十二！
Five hundred grand? That's over 12% of our budget!
一个人捐这么多钱
If you were donating that much,
为什么要匿名？
why would you do it anonymously?
很简单
Obvious reason.
- 什么？隐私？ - 不对
- What? Privacy?  - No.
当你的身份被泄露的时候 你会显得很高尚
It makes you look noble when you leak your identity.
我的天啊 你生来就这么愤世嫉俗吗？
Oh, my God. Were you born that cynical?
这只是一个用来形容…
That is just a word to denote the absence...
你是觉得我太天真烂漫了吗？好吧 我知道了
Of the naivety I so keenly exhibit? Yeah, right.
三秒后开始直播
Back on in three, people.
你从什么时候开始 不敢面对镜头了？
Since when were you camera-shy?
发生什么了？长皱纹了？
What happened? You find a wrinkle?
你可真是比尔·桑福德的走狗
If it isn't Bill Sandford's poodle.
让我猜猜 被人套着绳子
Let me guess, on a tight leash,
靠闻别人屁眼需求工作？
sniffing at his ass for business?
如果不是你这么可笑
If you weren't such a joke,
我们早就跟他合作了
we'd already have his business.
这样如何？
So how about this?
让小斯隆休息一天
Give Mini-Me a day off,
我让你上次头版头条
and I'll give you a shot at the title.
电视辩论直播赛 我和你
Live TV debate, you and me.
你居然想给我直播时间
You must be desperate
你肯定是憋坏了
if you're willing to give me airtime.
我好好地修理你一顿
I kick your bony ass hard enough,
比尔·桑福德就会意识到
Bill Sandford will realize
他选择了我们 是多么明智
why he came to us in the first place.
不对 你想用我的强势 让他担心
Uh-uh. You need me strong to make him worried.
跟我正面交锋 你不会显得很强的
You're not looking so strong after a head-on with me.
好吧 我答应你 帮你安排一场
All right. I'll grant you a job interview
国家电视台的面试
on national television.
你可以好好展示一下 你是多么忠诚的一条狗
You can show your master what a big, tough dog you are.
我们接下来要讨论的事情
What we're about to discuss
在办公室里只能通过代码
should only be referred to in code
或者邮件的形式进行交流
in the office and over e-mail.
我的前雇主们很会窃听和黑客技术
My ex-employers aren't beyond bugging and hacking.
你觉得我们的会议室里有窃听器？
You think our conference room is wearing a wire?
我们的目标人物是国家的参议员
We're gonna target a senator from a state
所以容不得半点闪失
we have zero right to swing.
天啊 你不是真的…
Oh, please, God, don't say...
阿尔贝托·戈麦斯 共和党人 弗罗里达
Alberto Gomez, Republican, Florida.
什么？
What'?
我还以为你要说密苏里
I thought you were gonna say Missouri.
弗罗里达不可能
Florida's preposterous.
我只是乐观而已
I'm being optimistic.
现在弗罗里达公众的意愿 对希顿·哈里斯是排斥的
Public opinion runs against Heaton-Harris in Florida.
- 我们晚点再谈  - 在办公室里？
- Let's talk later.  - In the office?
我要如何表达自己的异议？用旗语？
How do I register my dissent? By semaphore?
艾利克斯 你负责广告横幅
Alex, you're in charge of ad banners,
两点去智威汤逊
you have a 2:00 at JWT.
上面要写两个电话号码
I want two phone pitches.
克拉拉 布莱恩 劳伦 你们是第一小组
Clara, Brian, Lauren, you're one.
辛西娅 埃斯米 弗兰克林 你们是第二小组
Cynthia, Esme, Franklin, you're two.
罗斯 记录两组的数据 行动起来
Ross, get stats to both. Come on, get to it.
你到底想干什么？
What the hell are you thinking?
你应该相信我
That you should let me do my job.
又不是针对科尔·克拉维茨
This ain't Cole Kravitz, damn it.
我们的客户是一个非营利团体
Our client's a non-profit,
不是什么钻钱眼里的企业
not some cashed-up conglomerate.
我卑微地在外面摇首乞怜
I'm hiding in the bushes with my begging bowl,
看到有钱人就往人身上扑
waiting to leap out at anyone who looks like money,
而你现在却为了一个轻率的计划
and you're getting ready to set fire
就想让这数百万给打水漂
to half a million dollars on some hare-brained...
这种特务式的行动 着实极具吸引力
I mean this James Bond shit's endearingly wacky,
但你如果真想扭转弗罗里达的意愿
but if you think you're seriously going to get
你这么做就是无用功
any traction out of Florida, you're way out.
鲁道夫 你当初请我来这里的时候
Rodolfo, it was explicit in your pitch to lure me here
就应该很相信我的能力
that you held a certain degree of trust
认为我可以引导好这次运动
in my ability to run this campaign.
乔治 是我
George, it's me.
我知道自己在做什么
I know what I'm doing.
我们要谈谈弗罗里达的事
We need to talk about Florida.
我从不轻率行事
And I don't do hare-brained.
好球
Fucking A right.
整个早上你都在球桌上狠狠修理我
From the way you been kicking my ass all morning,
我不禁开始怀疑
I'm starting to think
你不请自来 是不是就是想要我好看的
you invited yourself here just to kick my ass.
我个人很支持希顿·哈里斯
I'm personally in favor of Heaton-Harris.
我公开申明过 我的支持者也是
I've publicly declared, my voters are behind me.
你来就是想教训我的？
Did you want to meet just to kick my ass?
听着 你手里握有六票
Look, you're sitting on six votes.
桑福德并不蠢
Sandford's not a punk,
他知道反对派就指望这几票翻身
he knows the opposition's counting on them.
他也知道如果他们拿不到这六票
He also knows if they don't get them,
他们的运动就结束了
their campaign will be over.
那你想干什么？
So, what are you gonna do?
信手走进我的俱乐部
Walk into my club,
在台球桌上痛扁我一局
bend me over a green baize table,
然后高谈阔论自由一番？
and give me the spiel about freedom?
如果让自由主义者得逞
About how, if the liberals get their way,
再过个几百年
in a couple of hundred years,
第二修正案会连我们
the Second Amendment will enshrine
拿棒球棒的权利都要干预了？
our rights to bear baseball bats?
不 这番话得由你去跟
No, that's the argument you're gonna make
你“蓝狗联盟”的朋友们讲
to your friends in the Blue Dog Coalition
你要告诉他们 你改变阵营了
when you tell them you're changing your position.
比尔·桑福德在考虑支持一个新的候选人
Bill Sandford's thinking about backing a new candidate.
跟他同一阵营 非常有前途的西班牙人
One of their own. A real up-and-comer. Hispanic.
收到了八所常青藤大学的录取单
Got offers from eight Ivy League schools.
常青藤？
Ivy League schools?
你有看过我的支持率吗？
Have you seen my approval ratings, Pat?
他不是要对抗你
No, he's not running against you.
而是对抗你的儿子
He's running against your son.
枪支管制反对派需要你的支持 汉克
The gun lobby wants your support, Hank.
他们知道你儿子在竞选密歇根议员
They know your boy's running for Michigan.
他们会给他精挑细选一位对手
They'll handpick an opponent.
确保他拿到选票
Back him to the hilt.
我试过让桑德福别这么干 但是…
I tried to talk Sandford out of it, but...
胡说八道 康纳斯 你说不定
Bullshit, Connors, you probably
就是那个唆使他这么干的人 你个混蛋
put him up to it, you motherfucker.
对于支持率的事情
About those approval ratings.
你可以相信自己
You can go either way.
或者悄悄地改变阵营 保护你的儿子
Quietly recant, protect your son.
桑福德不会忘记的
Sandford won't forget it.
但如果你让他失望了…
You disappoint him...
他更不会忘记
He won't forget that, either.
匹兹堡怎么样了？
So, how was Pittsburgh?
你是联邦调查局的吗？
What are you, a Fed?
中大西洋女子协会执法机关的主席
The President of the Mid-Atlantic Association of Women
打电话过来感谢你请她吃的午饭
in Law Enforcement called to say thanks for lunch.
我怎么不知道她们也是计划中的一部分
I wasn't aware they were part of our plan.
反正吃得又不贵
It wasn't JWT.
只吃了三十分钟
It was a 30-minute lunch.
她们也不是计划的一部分
They're not a part of our plan,
所以我才没请她吃大餐
which is why it wasn't JWT.
就不允许我有自己的社交生活？
Am I not allowed a social life?
我还以为你没有
I didn't know you had one.
对于一个连会话主题
As someone who has her underlings
都要让自己下属准备的人来说
root for conversational topics.
我的朋友圈很小罢了
I maintain a small circle of allies.
是吗 只有警察和护士？
Uh-huh. Cops and nurses?
如果你想知道全部细节的话 我到时候写张清单给你
Well, I can provide a list if you require full disclosure.
我们开始吧
So, grand unveiling.
- 你也来吗？ - 我们有更重要的问题要解决
- You coming?  - We got a bigger problem.
你在跑来跑去 跟别人聚餐的时候
While you've been jetting around the country for lunch,
我们的对手可一点都没松懈
our opponents have been doing their job.
汉克·巴杰利 “蓝狗”的主席
Hank Badgley, Chairman of the Blue Dog,
他控制了…
who controls the votes of...
六个议员的选票 我知道这个人 他是站在我们这边的
Six Senators, I know who he is. He's in our pocket.
真的？你真以为这样？
Really? That what you think?
他之前是支持我们的 但现在来了个一百八十度大转弯
He was on board, but he just did a 180.
他说他想等等看
Says he wants to wait and see.
“等等看”顶多算九十度转弯吧
"Wait and see" is more like a 90.
我们追随的议员根本就没把这当正事
We're chasing Senators who are in play.
我们不能损失已经锁定了的七票
We can't afford to lose seven votes we had locked.
这个缺口是没办法填补的
We won't recover.
我们没有他宜哲支持的视频吗？
We have him on camera pledging support?
当然有
Absolutely.
那就让他看看我们的厉害
Then we'll have to make him feel it.
谢谢
Thank you.
艾利克斯 这些横幅真不错
Alex, these banners are good.
你能再说一遍吗
Could you say that again
这遍别说得那么惊讶？
and sound a little less surprised?
等等 这不对啊
Hold on, this can't be right.
- 戈麦斯议员…  - 我们不去弗罗里达了
- Senator Gomez...  - We're not going to Florida.
什么？
What?
放弃弗罗里达
Florida's out.
但你说过我们要去弗罗里达
But you said that we were going to Florida
说服戈麦斯…
to swing Gomez...
所有人翻到第九个标签的位置
Everyone turn to Tab 9, please.
我这里什么都没有
I don't have anything at Tab 9.
保安 封锁辛西娅·格林的办公桌
Security, lock down Cynthia Green's desk.
拿走她的文件和硬盘
Secure her files and her hard drives,
护送她离开公司
and escort her off the premises.
你的黑莓手机拿出来
Your Blackberry, now.
赶快！
Now!
快点走
Let's go.
他向我提供合作邀请
He offered me partnership track.
那祝你好运
Good luck with that.
清理办公室
Clear the office.
快点！所有人都出去
Come on, come on, come on! Everybody out.
我要把这个地方彻底清查一下
I'll have the place swept for taps.
听起来也像特务的活儿
Sounds like James Bond shit to me.
我们晚点再谈这个问题
We will talk about this later.
所有人 都离开这栋楼！
Come on, everybody, clear the building!
快走！都出去！
Let's go! Out! Come on!
真不敢相信去弗罗里达
I can't believe the whole
找戈麦斯这整件事都是个幌子
Gomez-Florida thing was a ruse.
我们出其不意地选择进攻科罗拉多
We're coming out of left field to take Colorado
让他们根本反应不过来
before they figure out which hole they got screwed in.
她怎么能这么做？
How could she do that?
谁会有这种想法？
How does someone even think like that?
或许是她太天真了
Maybe in her naivety,
以为这样对她的职业生涯有帮助吧
she figured it'd be good for her career.
我说的不是辛西娅
I wasn't talking about Cynthia.
早上好
Morning.
请坐
Please take a seat.
我们不是说做不到
We're not saying it can't be done.
只是风险很大
But it's risky.
- 我们只有一次机会  - 嘿！
- We only get one shot.  - Hey!
你被跟踪了？
Were you followed?
很明显
Evidently.
让他进来
Let him in.
你能庄严发誓
Do you solemnly swear
接下来所说的话
that you will tell the truth,
全部是事实真相 只有真话
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth,
否则会受到作伪证的惩罚？
upon pains and penalties of perjury?
我发誓
I do.
请说出你的全名
State your full name, please.
快看啊
Well, look at this.
鲁道夫·维托里奥·施密特
Rodolfo Vittorio Schmidt.
这部车应该不是改装的雪佛兰吧？
I'm guessing this gear ain't for tuning my '69 Chevy?
鲁道夫 这是我的非官方支持团队
Rodolfo, my unofficial support team.
大山姆
Big Sam.
小山姆
Little Sam.
在你和斯隆女士共事的这段时间以来
During the time that you worked alongside Miss Sloane,
你们有没有就运用
did you hold any discussions
非法监控技术
pertaining to the use
进行过讨论？
of illegal surveillance techniques?
你们团队有多大规模？
So, how big is your organization?
我们一共有六个人 四个执行外务
Well, there are six of us, four are out on assignment.
- 那你们是前…  - 国家安全局员工
- And you're ex...  - NSA.
巴杰利突然改变了阵营
Badgley is flip-flopping.
最快让他回心转意的方法
But, quickest way to get him in line
就是挖掘出他的丑闻
is to mine for sordid details,
并且让他知道 我们掌握了这些信息
and then let him know we're in possession of them.
施密特先生 你们有吗？
Mr. Schmidt, did you?
有过 议员
Yes, Senator, we did.
他们是通过何种方法
And what means did they have at their disposal
实施这种监控手段的？
to carry out these surveillance practices?
标准全天二十四小时的音像监控
Standard 24-hour video and audio surveillance,
包括黑入手机和网上账户
cell phone and online account hacking,
实施位置跟踪 再加上我们最新的科技
location tracking, and, with our latest tech,
近距离窃听 何时何地都可以
close-quarters audio, anytime, anyplace.
你有听说过“不被察觉的窥探者”吗？
You ever hear the expression "Fly on the wall"?
来看看我们最新型的窃听技术
Well, meet the cutting edge in eavesdropping.
是只蟑螂
It's a cockroach.
可以用这个把它变换为
Which can be retro-fitted
可受控的机器蟑螂
as a cybernetic robo-roach with this.
我们把电极用胶水黏在它的触须上
We glue electrodes to its antennae,
在胸腔上穿孔
perforate the thorax,
这样就能控制它的运动轨迹
and we can control its movement remotely.
别给动物保护协会打电话 施密特
Don't call PETA, Schmidt.
这些小家伙可以飞檐走壁
These guys can crawl under doors,
无孔不入 根本不会被人察觉
into crevices, bags, completely undetected.
几个星期不进食 仍然保持很高的活力
They can go weeks without food and still be mobile.
那你对这些可能性是如何反应的？
And how did you react to the possibility of all this?
我告诉她这很令人惊异 也很有创意
I told her it was mind-boggling, ingenious,
但在道德上是很令人反感 且不能接受的
morally repugnant and completely unacceptable.
砰！
Boo!
你现在说的是勒索
You're talking about blackmailing
一个美国参议员
a United States Senator.
如果这个消息被泄露出去 你知道会造成怎样的损害吗？
Have you any idea of the damage if this ever came out?
不能重新赢回巴杰利 这造成的损害更大
No more than the damage done if we don't get Badgley back.
你们的手段和能力
Without prejudice to the undoubtedly
毫无疑问 非常一流
stellar job that you guys do.
但我们的公司有自己的
Our firm has certain standards
规定和原则 我不想轻易越界
below which I'm not prepared to stoop.
让我出去
Let me out of here.
施密特
Schmidt.
想其他办法
Find another way.
密歇根议员 汉克·巴杰利
It was a rude awakening
突然醒悟 今天他被一群有组织的
for Michigan Senator, Hank Badgley, today
枪支管制支持者 从他家里一直围堵到…
as he was tailed from his home to his workplace by this...
这他妈什么情况？
What the fuck is that?
…他的办公室
Organized by gun safety campaigners
他们想要议员就因为受到
in response to what they perceive
卑鄙之人的影响
as a U-turn on his support...
这是真的吗… 我他妈真不敢相信！
Can you believe... I do not fucking believe!
…而转变立场一事作出回应
In the shadow of a giant rat.
各个国家新闻的专题都在播这件事
It's on all of the national news outlets.
她到底是怎么做到的？
How the hell did she manage that?
不是她 是群众自己的选择
She didn't. They swing left all on their own.
这件事都有推特主题了
It has its own Twitter feed.
什么？
Huh?
“叛徒”
The rat.
说真的 有人在背后搞鬼促使我改变立场
Really, I think that this whole rat business
这种说法 其实只是一个很不幸的误会
is little more than an unfortunate misunderstanding.
我是参议院中第一个公开申明
I was one of the first members of the senate
支持希顿·哈里斯的成员
to lend my support to Heaton-Harris.
我一直都觉得这条法案
I've always maintained that
对公共安全有很重要的指导意义
the Bill is integral to public safety,
所以我对它的支持将不会动摇
and my support for it is unwavering.
现在 我希望大家能
Now, I sincerely hope that
忘掉这一切的流言蜚语…
we can get past all this silliness...
还有三名“蓝狗”的议员
Three more Blue Dog Senators
在下周要举办新闻发布会
have press conferences scheduled for next week.
一定要再三强调
Keep hammering the point
我们的本意不是财产没收
that we're not arguing for confiscation.
希顿·哈里斯的重点是在于…
Heaton-Harris is about stopping...
阻止罪犯和精神病患者
Criminals and psychopaths.
我现在已经上手了 莉斯
Yeah, I'm a pro at this now, Liz.
里面见
I'll see you in there.
你是什么时候知道有人泄密的？
So you knew there was a leak from when?
- 你说什么？ - 辛西娅
- Sorry?  - Cynthia.
你是什么时候怀疑 有人泄密的？
When did you start to suspect there was a leak?
美国医生联盟 凑资晚会之后
Uh, after the UAPD fundraiser.
然后你就让私人侦探去跟踪她？
And you had her followed by a Pl?
你怎么知道是她？
How did you know it was her?
什么？
Sorry?
泄密的人 你派人监视辛西娅
The leak, you had Cynthia watched.
你怎么知道是她？
How did you know it was her?
我不知道
I didn't.
我们全部人都被你监视了？
You had us all watched?
您好
Howdy.
卡尔·斯奈德 我是做银行保险的
Cal Sneider, banking and actuarial.
我们之前见过
I'm sure we've been introduced,
不过我忘了你的名字了
but your name escapes me.
抱歉 你认错人了
I'm sorry, you have the wrong person.
我绝对没有
I'm pretty sure I don't.
我这人认人很准的
Have a good memory for faces.
像你这么漂亮 我更不会忘了
This one I wouldn't readily forget.
真的 斯奈德先生
Really, Mr. Sneider,
你一定是认错人了
I've no idea who you think I am.
我先走了
Excuse me.
你知道现在这个时候
Uh-huh. You know we're not really
我们没必要进行这段对话 对吧？
supposed to be having this conversation, right?
俄勒冈州一半的土地 都是受联邦政府保护的
Half of Oregon is protected Federal parkland.
他们没办法拉拢
They can't develop it.
那边的州预算都是来自于伐木税收
So, state budgets come from logging revenues.
- 这我知道…  - 莉斯？
- got it...  - Liz?
你现在先不要想这些 这次辩论与此无关
Whatever clearing your head looks like, this isn't it.
所以说伐木工是非常重要的人群
So, loggers are a very influential group.
打扰一下！
Excuse me!
能来个人帮她化下妆吗？
Can someone have her makeup done, too, please?
我又不上电视！
I'm not a part of this!
摄影棚到处都是摄像机 你也要注意形象
You're a public figure in a room full of cameras.
是她吗？
IS that her?
莉斯？
Liz?
快叫布莱恩去联系那些伐木工
Hey, we have to get Bryan on these loggers.
我们马上去处理那些伐木工！
We're on top of the goddamn loggers!
你先给我集中注意！
Just clear your head!
稍等一下
One moment.
别胡思乱想 照我说的做
Clear your head, like I told you.
喂？
Hello?
- 好了  - 欢迎你 斯隆女士
- Fine.  - Ms. Sloane, welcome.
帕特 请坐
Pat. Please, take a seat.
我知道星期五就是提交日期了
I know Friday's Filing Day
你们组织的运动马上就要结束了
and your campaign will be over,
但如果你认为我会就此放水的话
but if you're thinking I'm gonna go easy,
那你就想多了
I can't do that.
这是现场直播 注意你们的用词
This is live TV, so no colorful language.
居然拉我的下属下水
Bullshit job offers to my staff,
你可真是无耻到新下限了
you've plumbed new depths.
那个自以为是的小姑娘？得了吧
A giant inflatable rodent? Please.
你毁了那个女孩的前程
You ruined that girl's career.
好了 都给我闭嘴 开始吧！
All right, shut up, the both of you. Let's go!
大家好 我是乔恩·欧尼尔
Hello, America, I'm Jon O'Neill,
欢迎收看《华盛顿周报》特别版节目
welcome to a special edition of This Week In Washington.
枪支！多点还是少点好？
Guns! More or Less?
去年一共发生了三百七十二起大型的枪击案
There were 372 mass shootings last year,
六十五起校园枪击案
64 school shootings,
在美国一共有超过三亿支枪支…
and there are over 300 million guns in our country...
你以前跟康纳斯共事过？
You used to work with Connors?
整整四年
Four years.
满嘴脏话 出其不意 但非常有效率
Foul-mouthed, unexpected, and very effective.
如果要想背景调查落到实处
If background checks are to be of any use,
就应该对所有枪支买卖实行 而不是其中的一些
they should apply to all gun sales, not just some.
这难道不是希顿·哈里斯所推祟的吗？
Isn't that what Heaton-Harris is proposing?
没错 这条法案确实扩大了枪支管理的范围
Precisely. The bill expands the scope of gun regulation,
但它同时也是对美国宪法
and it's yet another affront
所规定的人民合法权利的公开冒犯
to Americans' Constitutional rights.
不对 这条法案非常有效地
No, the bill closes an absurd loophole
阻止了恐怖分子黑名单上的人
which allows people on terrorist watch-lists
在想买枪的时候 不用接受任何检查的漏洞
to buy guns without any checks whatsoever.
这是对权利政府所规定的的
It's an incursion into individual liberty
公民自由的一种亵渎…
by an all-powerful government...
- 什么 就像驾照一样？ - 驾照？
- What, like drivers' licenses?  - Drivers' licenses?
只有在经受严格的理论教育
It's illegal to operate a car
以及通过实践考试的人
without going through rigorous
才能开车 否则就是违法的
theoretical and practical assessments.
- 这条规则 很显然…  - “河豚厨师”
- That's a clear constraint...  - Fugu chefs.
…是对公民自由驱车权利的限制
On the freedom of individuals to drive cars,
- 或者开飞机也是一个道理  - 快说“河豚厨师”
- or pilots to fly planes.  - Come on. Fugu chefs.
在日本 一名厨师必须经过七年的训练
You know, in Japan, chefs train for seven years
才能为客人准备一种带毒的鱼
before they're allowed to serve
其名叫河豚
a poisonous blowfish called fug...
真棒！
Yes!
这跟做背景调查
What does any of this
有什么关系？
have to do with background checks?
这是个好问题
Is a fair question.
在座的各位
Does anyone in this room
有人觉得政府应该废除驾照吗？
think the government should abolish drivers' licenses?
- 这太荒唐了  - 为什么？
- That's absurd.  - Why?
驾照也是一种政府对公民自由权利的限制
They're a government incursion into individual liberty.
我们接受它 是因为它很有道理
We accept them because they make sense.
对于越危险的机器
The more dangerous the machinery,
就应该有更严格的测试
the more rigorous the tests should be.
我觉得我们可以把 对危险机器的定义
I think we can extend our definition
扩展到半自动武器上来
of dangerous machinery to semi-automatic firearms.
但是宪法的第二修正案并没有
Except that the Second Amendment to the Constitution
保护公众驾车的权利
doesn't guarantee the right to drive cars,
或者操纵机器 亦或是处理河豚
or operate machinery or serve blowfish for that matter.
但它保护了公民买枪和持枪的权利
It guarantees the right to keep and bear arms.
是你最近没有好好翻阅吧
Perhaps you haven't read it lately.
修正案中没有任何
Nothing in the bill
限制公民买枪及持枪的合法权利
infringes the rights of the people to keep and bear arms.
第二修正案签署于
The Second Amendment was signed in a time
一个平均年龄只有三十八岁的年代
where the average life expectancy was 38,
而且在那个年代 我们的开国元勋
and it was common practice for our Founding Fathers
如若发生冲突 他们都愿意选择通过战争来解决
to resolve their differences at dawn in a gunfight.
那条法案或许适用于 当时的世界格局和社会状态
What may have been perfectly sensible in those alien times
但对于现在处理问题的方式 未必适用
is wholly inadequate to solve the problems of the present.
这不是预演好的辩词 她在干什么？
That's not the rebuttal, what's she doing?
美国宪法经受住了
The United States Constitution
时间的考验
has stood the test of time.
它给公民授予的权利是不可置疑的
It's authored to confer unimpeachable rights,
而这种效应不会随着
which don't change depending
时代的变迁而被撼动
on which way the Wind's blowing.
这种权利也能让别有意图的
It's so authored with the specific intent
比如全世界
of keeping at bay
像伊丽莎白·斯隆这种
the Elizabeth Sloanes of this world,
想拿宪法擦屁股的人干瞪眼
who wanna wipe their asses with the Constitution...
好了 我们先…
Okay, let's...
…他们的主观意念 是无法动摇它的
and replace it with their own judgment,
因为他们自以为比这个伟大国家的
because she knows better than
开国元勋更了解这个世界
the Founding Fathers of this great nation.
没有什么是不可置疑的 包括宪法
Nothing is unimpeachable, not even the Constitution.
刚刚你迫不及待 用来反驳我的权利声明
It's ironic that the very statement of rights
事实上
you're so quick to invoke
都只是修正案里的条目
is in fact an Amendment.
抱歉纠正一下 伊丽莎白
I may not like it either, Elizabeth,
那是第二修正案
but it's the Second Amendment.
言论自由 宗教自由 新闻自由 这些是公认的
Comes right after freedom of speech, religion, and press,
搜索自由稍有限制
and somewhere before freedom from search
是否做对自己不利的证明 也有选择的自由
and from having to testify against yourself.
这些东西组合在一起
They're all sort of bunched together.
构成了人权法案
It's called the Bill of Rights.
- 你准备怎么回答？ - 没这个必要
- How do you get around that?  - We don't need to.
最高法院已经做出表态
Supreme Court already made it clear
针对公众持枪的权利
that the right to own a gun
需要经受合法的限制
is subject to lawful restriction.
其中一条就是背景调查
One of those is background checks.
全面的背景调查就是一种侵犯
Universal background checks are an infringement.
“不容侵犯的部分”这句话
What part of "shall not be infringed"
你没看到吗？
don't you get?
我觉得那是里面最无力 也是最令人厌恶的
I get that that's the weakest, most mind-numbing retort
反驳论点
in your impoverished arsenal.
毫无论点可言
Sort of a last refuge for those
根本无法令人信服
with no real argument at all.
你现在说的
You're talking about
可是美国宪法
the United States Constitution.
如果他们能提出合理的论据
If they could produce a rational winning argument,
我很乐意改变我的想法
I'd gladly migrate to their side,
但单纯只是“因为宪法里 圣经上 还有占星术”
but "because it says so in the Constitution,
“是这么说的” 就盲目追崇 这根本就不能让人信服！
"the Bible, or my horoscope," it's not a winning argument!
那只是自我高潮
It's a ripcord.
就好像一个穿着妈妈裙子
An intellectual equivalent of a yellow,
胆怯 只知道尿裤子的弱智
pant-pissing wimp cowering behind mommy's skirt.
- 我们先进段广告吧  - 不 我们继续！
- Why don't we bring this back.  - No, no, no. Let's not!
我们为何不问问那些母亲们
Why don't we ask all the mothers out there
他们的孩子被武装反社会份子枪杀
who lost their children to an armed sociopath,
问问她们觉得 宪法规定的
if they believe in his unimpeachable
且不可置疑的持枪权利 是否合理？
Constitutional right to bear arms?
为什么不问问那个躲在
Why not ask the terrified girl
门卫储物室 眼睁睁看着自己的同学
who locked herself in a janitor's closet
被惨杀的
at Bloomington High,
被吓得魂飞魄散的
forced to listen
布卢明顿中学的女孩？
as her peers were being massacred?
去啊 问问她！
Go ahead, ask her!
她的名字叫作埃斯米·曼尼克瑞安
Her name is Esme Manucharian.
她就站在那里！
She's standing right there!
我的天啊 莉斯
Jesus Christ, Liz.
好了 时间到！
Okay, time out!
我们先休息一下 广告之后回来
We're going to take a break, and when we come back,
希望到时候两位能
maybe these two will stop playing
停止开黄腔 围绕实事进行讨论
Patty Cake and the blowfish really come off.
马上回来！
Be right back!
如果只是一时冲动
I won't insult your intelligence
我是不会把你的信息透露出去 让你难堪的
by claiming that came out in the heat of the moment.
什么时候计划的？
How far back?
我开始适应面对媒体的时候？
Once I started getting used to all the media?
原来一开始都是你计划好的
Okay. Day one.
哇
Wow.
那晚吃晚餐的时候…
At dinner that night...
你问我如果这是决定成败的关键
You asked me if I'd go public
我是否愿意公开这件事
if it was the difference between victory and defeat.
如果我当时说不呢？
What if I'd said no?
你还是会说出来？
Would you still have done it?
可能会
Probably.
我受聘是来赢的
I was hired to win,
我有责任
and I have a responsibility
动用身边的一切资源
to use whatever resource I have.
这件事能让我们博得很多关注
The press we're going to get from this,
如果不说出来 就是玩忽职守了
it's practically a dereliction of duty not to use it.
就这样？我只是你的“资源”？
That's it? I'm a "resource"?
专业上来讲 是的
Professionally, yes.
我理解你有自己的情感 有自己的生活
I understand you have feelings, and a life,
但我对它们并不负有责任
but I have no duty to them.
我只对这个案子负责 如果两者发生冲突
I have a duty to the cause, and if the two conflict,
我只能选择更重要的那个
there will only ever be one winner.
感谢你的直言直语
Well, hooray for straight talk.
好了
Okay.
准备好 埃斯米 我们需要发布一条声明
Get ready, Esme. Network wants a statement.
把妆补好 我们要手挽手走出去
Re-apply your makeup. We'll walk out arm-in-arm.
简短有力就行 不用接受提问
We'll be brief. No questions.
今晚 让我们给大家点好戏看看
Tonight, we'll leave them wanting more.
首先
First of all,
我先声明 我把自己的一生都贡献给了
I want to make it clear that I have dedicated my life
讨论枪支安全的议题 因为现在的系统是残缺的
to gun safety issues because the current system is broken.
这是我很理智的判断
That's a rational judgment.
而不是感性使然
Not an emotional one.
我是一九九八年
I am a survivor
布卢明顿中学惨案的幸存者
of the Bloomington High School massacre of 1998.
很多年来 我一直都压抑自己的痛苦
For years, I sought to hide the pain and the trauma,
害怕再回想起那时的经历
for fear of having to relive it.
但我逐渐意识到
But I've come to realize
还有成百上千枪支暴力的受害者
that the thousands of people affected by gun violence
我们应该站出来 让自己的声音被听到
need to stand up and be counted.
他们需要一个能
They need a representative
为这个团体发声的代表
who can speak out for what they have endured.
给桑福德打电话
Let's call Sandford.
一个能理解他们遭遇的人…
Someone who can relate their experience...
我们或许有赢的机会
There might be life in this yet.
…能把它分享给社会大众的人
To the public at large.
你真是个混蛋 伊丽莎白
You're a piece of work, Elizabeth.
如果为了赢 你想把自己往火坑里推
If you want to set yourself on fire
我不阻拦你 但你居然这么对埃斯米？
to service your need to win, I won't protest, but Esme?
我只在乎结果
The end is my concern.
你们这些崇尚自由主义的好好先生 只会循规蹈矩
You liberal goody-goodies can fret over the means.
- 你需要我  - 结果？
- You need me.  - The end?
你在国会翘着脚
It disappeared over the Hill
公开侮辱国家国法的时候 就已经没有结果了
when you cocked your leg and pissed all over the flag!
你居然把美国宪法比作占星术？
Comparing the United States Constitution to a horoscope?
枪支管制的反对派肯定乐死了
That's the kind of shit the gun lobby thrives on.
你到底有没有意识到 我们输定了？
Or have you realized by now we're going to lose anyway?
这比我的前途重要
This is more important than my career,
也比埃斯米每次面对记者
or Esme's unease at fighting reporters
诉说那些经历的不安感重要
every time she has to take out the trash.
- 你简直疯了  - 我们不会输
- You're out of control.  - We're not gonna lose.
如果我告诉你
What if I told you
整个策略都是一个骗局呢？
this whole strategy was a shell game?
只是演给公司里 其他像辛西娅·格林那样的人看的
For the benefit of the Cynthia Greens of this firm.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
比尔·桑福德说的没错
Bill Sandford was right.
女性才是枪支管制反对派的盲点
Women are the gun lobby's blind spot.
那是一股被他们忽视 而又不可控制的
A massive power base that they don't speak to
巨大的势力
and they can't control.
然后呢？
And?
还记得我那些奇怪的短途旅行吗？
Those strange excursions on my itinerary?
我都是去拜访女性代表 女权团体
Women's representative bodies, feminist groups,
还有女性总裁的
female CEOs.
我反复地游说她们
I've talked as many as I could
甚至威胁她们 往我的个人账户
into brow-beating their membership
捐钱
to donate to my PAC.
你还有个人账户？
You have a PAC?
提交日期那天 比尔·桑福德
Bill Sandford's getting a nasty surprise
会有个大惊喜
come filing day.
到底有多大？
How nasty are we talking?
来自三百万个捐赠者 捐献的一千五百万
Fifteen million from over three million donors-nasty.
三个月就这么多？
In one quarter?
事实上 时间更短
Actually, less.
真不敢相信
Unbelievable.
为什么现在告诉我？
Why are you telling me this now?
你之前一直瞒着我
You kept this from me all along,
为什么选择今晚告诉我？
and you're telling me tonight?
天啊 我才告诉你 我们又有赢的希望了
Oh, my God, I tell you we're back in the game,
你想说的就只有这个？
and all you can say is that?
你一开始就打算把埃斯米供出去
You knew you were gonna screw Esme tonight,
所以你才把这个消息瞒到现在
so you kept this from me to blindside me
为了让我不开除你
before I had a chance to fire you.
作为一个说客 你有着很不寻常的洞察力
You have unusual insight for a "boutique" lobbyist.
从开始到现在 都是你一个人在操控着一切
You've been pulling all the strings, all along.
游说的重点在于先见之明
Lobbying is about foresight.
你要预估你对手的行动 再制定应对的…
You anticipate your opponent's moves, you devise...
我他妈不是你的对手！
I am not your fucking opponent!
你有正常过吗？
Were you ever normal?
小时候呢？
As a child?
或者说这种扭曲的思维 在你还没出生前
Or were the twisted thought processes in your mind
就已经在你脑中滋生了？
hard-wired in the womb?
因为我真的搞不明白
Because I'm having a really hard time
为什么会有人有这样的思维
understanding how somebody gets to this.
可能我就是个混蛋吧
Guess I'm just a piece of work.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
你是玛德琳·伊丽莎白·斯隆
You're Madeline Elizabeth Sloane.
你工作于处理政府事务的交流公司
You work in government affairs at a communications company.
谷歌技术真好
Well googled.
那天是怎么回事？在凑资晚会上？
So what was that? At the fundraiser?
你装作不认识我的样子
You pretended like we're strangers.
不然你想我怎么反应？
What did you expect?
你没事吧？
You all right?
嗯…
Mmm...
唯一一个叫我玛德琳的人 就是我的母亲
The only person to call me Madeline was my mother.
政府事务和沟通交流
Government affairs and communications
都只是说客的褒义说法
are just fancy words for lobbying.
那说客又是什么的褒义说法？
And blowfish a fancy word for what, exactly?
离开这个房间 我们就是陌生人
Outside this room, we're strangers.
这就是我们这种关系的规则
Those were the rules of this engagement.
当时没人…
We were alone...
但那是公共场合
In a public place.
我不能在外面被人发现和你在一起
I can't be associated with you there.
说不定有人知道你的真实身份
At least one other person knew who you were.
那个女的是谁？
Who was she, anyway?
我不能泄露我的客户信息
I never reveal my clients. Ever.
你只喜欢到处打听她们的个人生活
You just, uh, pry into their personal lives,
在谷歌上搜索真相
blowfish for the truth.
我听说你们这些政客对真相好像不感兴趣
Yeah, I hear you lobbyists ain't so good with the truth.
你一个有着四重身份
Says the guy with four identities,
靠和陌生人上床赚钱的人 也敢这么说？
who sleeps with strangers for money?
我只是很惊讶 你怎么这么会说谎
I'm just surprised by what a natural bullshitter you are.
你就是说谎长大的 福德
I grew up lying, Forde.
我也不想 但我不得不这么做
Didn't want to. I had to.
所以我才会这么擅长
That's why I excel at it.
我也很愿意用这项技能
It's a skill I would've happily traded
交换一个正常的人生
for a normal life.
正常也没那么好
Normal's overrated.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
我做不到
But I can't.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
- 抱歉  - 今晚就算了
- I'm sorry.  - Forget about tonight.
怎么了？我做错什么了吗？
Why? I do somethin'?
不是的…
No, it's, um...
我现在没这个心情
I'm not in the right frame of mind.
给你
Here.
- 这应该是你赚过最容易的钱了  - 可我什么都没做
- Easiest money you ever made.  - I didn't do anything.
你如约出现了 而我浪费了你的时间
Well, you showed up, I wasted your time, so, yeah.
我们就坐下来谈谈也行
You know, we could just sit and talk, and...
拿好这该死的钱 福德！
Take the fucking money, Forde!
请你离开
Get out, please.
随便你吧
Suit yourself.
诺伊马克
Neumark.
- 米尔纳  - 来个人帮忙 快点
- Milner.  - Two hands here, come on.
- 科尔森…  - 韦德·鲍威尔 弗吉尼亚
- Carlson...  - Wade Powell, Virginia.
还有哈克曼
Hackman's come over too.
我们失去了米尔纳 诺伊马克 科尔森 还有哈克曼
We've lost Milner, Neumark, Carlson, Hackman.
阿达莫的主任说他的立场也开始动摇了
Adamou's chief of staff said he's softening his position.
- 艾利克斯？ - 我来给他的屁眼松松土…
- Alex?  - I'll soften his fuckin'...
比尔·桑德福在三号线
Bill Sandford's on line 3.
马上让阿达莫关门
Closing Adamou right the fuck now.
她偷走了我的点子
She takes my own idea
升级之后又用来对抗我们
and goes up against us with it.
我们早就警告过你 比尔
We did try to warn you, Bill.
来自三百万个捐赠者的一千五百万
Fifteen million. From three million donors.
在不到三个月的时间里
In less than a quarter.
你要是能阻止她 就能阻止希顿·哈里斯
You stop her, you stop Heaton-Harris.
你必须谨慎行事
We have to make it personal now.
她现在可是关注的焦点
She becomes the story.
我们可以动用媒体关系 比尔
We can use our media relationships, Bill,
让她处于劣势
put her on the defensive.
我不仅仅想打压她
I don't just want her on the defensive.
也不仅想从运动中把她除掉
I don't just want her off the campaign.
我想让她成为杀一儆百的例子 让其他人看看
I want her to be the reason that people think twice
和第二修正案作对 会有什么后果
before taking on the guardians of the Second Amendment.
我要毁了她的前途
I want her career.
艾利克斯 是我 我刚刚下飞机
Hey, Alex, it's me. I just landed.
费城和我想象中一样 是个好地方
Philadelphia was as good as what we could have hoped for.
- 现在情况如何？ - 还有四票就搞定了
- So how are we doing?  - That's four to go, people.
不是开玩笑的吧
You're kidding me.
哇 真是太棒了
Wow, that's amazing.
好了
All right.
我们请来了埃斯米·曼尼克瑞安
We're joined now by Esme Manucharian.
埃斯米 谢谢你加入我们
Esme, thanks for joining us.
你觉得之前针对枪支的辩论
Would you say that the gun debate is now
已经上升到女权的问题了吗？
largely become a women's issue?
你只需要看看数据
You need only look at the numbers
就能发现枪支安全问题
to see that gun safety has become
已经变成美国女性所面临的首要问题
a deciding issue for American women.
如果众议员不理会问题的真实存在
If their representative isn't listening,
我们就会通过民意投票 选出能为我们做主的代表
they'll go to the polls and elect someone who will.
你想干什么？
What do you want?
我有整整一千五百万可以挥霍
I got 15 million to blow.
劳伦在筛选你的信件
Lauren was going through your letters.
在满满一信箱的死亡威胁信和僧恨信中 她找到了这封
Between the death threats and the hate mail, she found this.
《前哨报》的布鲁·沃尔什
Pru Walsh of The Sentinel is doing
正在做游说业的专题报道
a feature on the lobbying industry.
她想找你
That means you.
如果她真想见我 何必写信给我？
Well, if she wants to meet me, why did she send a letter?
因为她不是真的想见你
Because she doesn't really want to meet you.
她说她想联系你 安排一次采访
She wants to say she reached out to you
但是并没收到回信
for an interview, but didn't hear back.
这是对别人的侮辱
It's a takedown.
至少我们还能让她失望
Well, the least we can do is disappoint her.
去安排吧
Set it up.
我取消了你十点的安排
I've canceled your 10:00 a.m.
去跟我们的内部律师见个面
You're gonna see our in-house attorney.
真不敢相信你们居然见过面
I don't believe you two have met.
你知道我对这件事的态度
You know how I feel about this.
我一开始就反对你招她进来
I was against you ever hiring her.
因为你的工作 不是赢得游说战
Because your job is not winning lobbying fights,
而是防止让我们变得…
your job is to stop us from getting...
对她这么卑鄙的行为 你居然睁一只眼闭一只眼
Quite independently of her being utterly contemptible.
你到底在想什么？
What the hell were you thinking?
不管原因是什么
You know, whatever it was,
现在看起来都很愚蠢
I guess it seems pretty stupid now.
莉斯 来见见你的律师
Liz, meet your protection.
丹尼尔·波斯纳 法律部主管
Daniel Posner, Head of Legal.
莉斯·斯隆 行为可鄙的累赘
Liz Sloane, contemptible liability.
也是一个业余唇语爱好者
And amateur lip-reader.
建一面玻璃墙 这到底是谁的主意？
Whose idea were the glass walls? Seriously?
明天还要上两个电视节目
Two TV slots tomorrow,
一个广播台节目 之后就可以离开伊利诺斯了
then a radio thing, and finally I'm done in Illinois.
你现在在哪儿？
Where are you?
金石餐厅 等着他们上菜
Gold Stone, waiting for them to hurry up
他们速度太慢了
and invent the food pill.
那可能得等一会
That may take a while.
然后一边在计划如何让最后的四个议员支持我们
And plotting to ensnare our last four senators.
现在已经拿下五十六人 还剩四人 我们的表现已经非常… 噢！
Fifty-six down, four to go. We're actually doing... Oh!
- 对不起  - 抱歉 对不起
- I'm sorry.  - I'm so sorry. My fault.
- 谢谢你  - 给你
- Thanks. Thank you.  - Here you go.
好的
Okay.
不好意思
Sorry about that.
还记得第一天的时候 我问你我们该如何取胜时
Remember that first day when I asked how do we win,
你回答我“事实上 我们赢不了”吗？
and you said "Realistically, we don't"?
每一个字我都记得清清楚楚
I stand by every word of that.
不好意思？
Excuse me?
所以那一千五百万 你想就这么轻描淡写一笔带过？
So you're going to downplay the 15 million?
是啊 我们要保持低调
Yeah, 'cause we can't sound like
不能让别人以为我们太自以为是了
we're bragging about how much we're pulling in.
议员会根据捐款情况 决定自己的投票意图
Senators link donations to voting intention,
在这之前 我们不能说错话…
we can't say anything that might stop...
你想尝尝子弹吗 婊子？
You wanna take this, bitch?
嗯？
Huh?
埃斯米 你在听吗？
Esme, you're still there?
来啊
Come on.
尝尝啊
Take it.
埃斯米？发生什么事了？
Esme? What the hell was that?
你经历过这种情况 对吧？
You been here before, right?
埃斯米？
Esme?
看着我！
Look at me!
埃斯米？
Esme?
但这次我要你的命
Except I'm gonna do it right this time.
我现在所站的位置
I'm standing at the scene
就是昨晚发生枪击案的现场
of last night's shooting.
我们了解到 袭击者的目标
We understand that the assailant
是枪支管制运动中的领导人物
was targeting a leading figure in the gun control movement,
但最后袭击者被一名手持
and was then shot dead by a civilian
实名登记过的手枪的市民击毙
carrying a registered, concealed firearm.
这位好心人的名字叫作…
The name of the vigilante has yet to be revealed...
乔治？
George?
你在看新闻吗？
You're watching the news?
比尔·桑福德的好日子
Yeah, whole bunch of Christmases
提前来了
just came early for Bill Sandford.
我正在往机场赶 准备出去好好潇洒一下
I'm headed to the airport. Get ready to spend some money.
警察确认了该位市民的身份 他叫弗兰克·麦吉尔
Police have confirmed his identity as Frank McGill.
麦吉尔的手枪是登记过的 是合法的
McGill was a legal owner of a registered weapon.
希顿·哈里斯对他构不成影响
Heaton-Harris wouldn't have touched him.
但对另一个混蛋
But it might have made it harder
就没那么容易了
for the other son of a bitch.
我们对这个人有什么了解？他是从哪里买来的枪？
What do we know about him? Where'd he get his piece?
他的地下室是不是私藏了很多武器…
Did he have an arsenal stashed in his basement...
由于第二修正案的存在
For the Second Amendment,
才使她在面对精神有问题的人时
which guaranteed her right to be protected
能够受到保护
from a sick individual.
最重要的是 给像弗兰克·麦吉尔
And most of all, for Frank McGill.
这样有警戒心 负责任 且枪法准的模范市民
Model citizen, vigilant, responsible,
提供了救人的机会
and his aim is true.
你还好吗？
How are you doing?
你要回家吗？
You heading home?
你订了华盛顿来的往返机票
You make a round-trip from D.C.
就是想来候机室盯住我？
to pin me in a departure lounge?
好确定我有按照你的剧本走？
So you can check me off your list?
我背叛了你的信任 我想陪你回去
I betrayed your confidence. I set you down this path.
“没关系 莉斯 这不是你的错”
"Don't worry, Liz, it's not your fault."
这就是你想听到的回答吗？
ls that what you wanna hear?
“你怎么可能预先想到？”
"How could you possibly have known?"
我是不会这么说的
You're not gonna get it.
他想杀了我
He wanted to kill me.
我不知道界限在哪 埃斯米
I didn't know where the line was, Esme.
我从来都不知道界限在什么地方
I never, never know where the line is.
你想休息多久都行
Obviously, take all the time you want.
等你准备好了
And when you're ready,
我们很欢迎你 重新加入
we'd love to have you back on the campaign.
这次由你自己选择
Your own terms.
不用面对媒体 你做幕后工作也行
No media, you can work behind the scenes.
如果你不想和我共事
If you don't want to work with me,
我就辞职
I'll resign from the campaign.
如果这是你所希望的
If that's what you want.
这就是你求我回去工作的办法？
Is that your move to get me back at my desk?
你想让我面对摄像头
You want me in front of a camera
和弗兰克·麦吉尔对峙？
to counter Frank McGill?
我甚至想过 这一切都是你策划的
It even crossed my mind that this was all you.
你只是没想到
You just didn't account
在我身后真的出现了一个持枪的人
for an armed civilian right behind me.
埃斯米…
Esme...
我会继续战斗的 伊丽莎白
I'll keep fighting, Elizabeth.
只要是我能出力的地方都行
Wherever I can make a difference.
但前提是 离你远远的
But as far as possible away from you.
当你停止以尊重待人的时候
You crossed the line when you stopped
你就已经越界了
treating people with respect.
你足够聪明 一定早就意识到这一点了
You're smart enough to know that.
你只是不在乎罢了
You just don't care.
谢谢 谢谢大家 欢迎回来
Thank you, thank you. Welcome back.
我们的下一位嘉宾
Our next guest this morning is
是那种在你下班回家路上
the kind of guy you'd want to have around
突然遇见一个人 拿枪指着你的脸
when you're walking home from work one night
你一定希望他出现在你身边的人
and some dude sticks a gun in your face.
在结束了军旅生涯之后
After his military career,
麦吉尔做了一名商业飞行员…
McGill worked as a commercial pilot...
各位 面对现实吧 现在大街上已经不安全了
Let's face it, folks, the streets ain't safe.
要不是我们接下来这位勇敢 无畏
And if it wasn't for the courage, bravery,
且枪法准的嘉宾
and damn fine aim of our next guest,
就会有另一场悲剧发生
we'd be reflecting on yet another tragedy.
女士们先生们 掌声欢迎
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome
最近的大红人 弗兰克·麦吉尔
the man of the moment, Frank McGill.
弗兰克·麦吉尔 你真是全美英雄
So, Frank McGill, all-American hero.
算不上 我只是一个在
Not at all. An ordinary guy
合适的时间 合适的地点 出现了的普通人
in the right place at the right time.
在他的皮带下面 放了一颗子弹
TALK SHOW HOST 1 With a 9 milli. under his belt.
我很好奇 你之前救的那个人曾领导过
I'm curious. The person whose life you saved once campaigned
废除携带枪支条令的活动
for a ban on concealed carry.
你对此作何感想？
How do you feel about that?
我很反对这样的观点
I respectfully disagree with those views.
但那位小姐有权利坚持自己的主观
But the young lady is entitled to her opinion
没有人可以因为这一点 而去攻击她
and nobody should be attacking her for that,
更别说拿枪去威胁她
much less holding her at gunpoint.
麦吉尔是上帝的礼物
McGill's a gift from God.
但效应并不会长久
But it won't last forever.
我们在计划来发大的
We're looking to parlay that
更进一步地考验这个斯隆
into a closer examination of Sloane.
我在考虑办一场国会听证会
I'm thinking of a Congressional hearing
来会会她另类的游说技巧
into her unorthodox lobbying practices.
我肯定能找到一个愿意接受这个方案的议员
I'm sure we can find a senator who may be open to the idea.
你想在媒体面前泼她脏水
You want to talk trash about her in the press,
这是一回事
that's one thing.
但国会听证会需要
A Congressional hearing requires
我们有确实的 关于她不正当行为的证据
a convincing allegation of impropriety.
如果能让她脸面全无 我举双手赞成
I'd give my left nut to drag her rep through the dirt,
但这是不可能的事
but you're not gonna get it.
她是开脱罪责的专家
She's a CYA specialist.
我从没见过像她那样擅于卖弄学问的人…
I've never met anyone so pedantic...
快开始全面调查
Start an inquisition.
让我们看看 她究竟有多会隐藏自己的污点
Let's see how well-covered her ass really is.
嗨
Hi.
我是布鲁·沃尔什 谢谢你们能来
Pru Walsh. Thanks so much for coming over.
这位是来自法律部的麦克·戈登
This is Mike Gordon from our legal department.
这位是我们法律部的丹尼尔·波斯纳
Daniel Posner from ours.
斯隆女士 你是这个行业里
Miss Sloane, you're at the forefront
最具关注度的人物 但你的名声却很臭
of an industry with a terrible reputation.
你有想过为什么吗？
Do you think that's deserved?
这项法案在过去几年 没被推翻的唯一原因
The only reason this bill wasn't passed decades ago
就是它能够满足某些权势的特殊利益
is because of the power of special interests.
当一个说客在凑集资金时…
When a lobbyist raises finance...
在袭击案发生后 都没有看到
We haven't heard from Esme Manucharian
埃斯米·曼尼克瑞安 你有和她联系过吗？
since the attack. Are you in contact with her?
这是我的私事
That's a private matter.
我觉得非常重要的一点…
I think what's important to remember...
那你有跟她沟通过吗？
So have you talked to her at all?
值得注意的一点就是 这个弗兰克·麦吉尔
What is important to remember here is that Frank McGill
恰巧就是守法 并且负有责任的
is exactly the kind of law-abiding,
枪支拥有者
responsible gun owner
而这种人的权利 是受到希顿·哈里斯的保护的
whose rights the Heaton-Harris Bill protects.
你对发生的一切内疚吗？
Do you feel any guilt about what happened?
我为什么要感觉内疚？
Why would I feel guilt?
你让埃斯米当你们运动的门面
You made Esme the face of your campaign.
是你在那次辩论赛上
You thrust her into the limelight
把她推向风口浪尖的
that night on the debate.
- 我不想谈这件事  - 你也不需要回答
- I'm not talking about this.  - You don't have to.
对于你要让她在国家电视台露面一事
Did she know that you were going to
她知情吗？她有同意吗？
out her on national TV? Did she agree to that?
你为什么不报道一下 多数的枪支拥有者
Why not report that the majority of gun owners
更支持全面的背景调查呢？
favor more extensive background checks?
她可能整个职业生涯
She probably went her entire career
都在小心地守护自己这个秘密
trying to keep that a carefully guarded secret.
反对枪支管制的人只会用花言巧语
That the gun lobby's fear-mongering rhetoric
传播一些谣言 抹黑希顿·哈里斯法案
is trying to paint Heaton-Harris into something it's not.
你觉得是不是因为你把她的秘密揭露了
Do you think that your little revelation
才致使她成为被袭击目标的？
is what made her a target?
很明显 斯隆女士
It's clear Miss Sloane
现在不想谈关于曼尼克瑞安小姐的事
doesn't wish to discuss Ms. Manucharian.
更明显的是 你的文章
What's really clear is that
早就已经写好了
your article's already written.
别回答这个问题
Don't respond to that.
你的这些言论纯属肆意推测
That's purely speculative on your part.
- 你的领导是谁？ - 别这样
- Who's controlling you?  - Let's not do this.
事实就是 你根本不会知道
Look, the fact is, you have no way of knowing
沃尔什女士的意图…
what Ms. Walsh intends to do...
真正的事实是 你们对斯隆女士
The fact is that you have no interest
将要讲的话根本就没有兴趣
in what Miss Sloane has to say.
- 你怎么知道？ - 你的录音机已经关了
- And how would you know that?  - Your Dictaphone's off.
太丢脸了
Takedown.
这还算好的了
It could've been worse.
我现在已经发现四处事实错误了
I've got four factual errors so far.
这对你影响不好 莉斯
This is not good, Liz.
都扔进碎纸机里去吧
Dump it in the recycling.
还能多造几支铅笔出来
They'll make pencils out of it.
说不定其中一支就能
Maybe one will find its way into
跑到一个真正有职业道德的记者手上
the hands of a reporter with some integrity.
这些负面影响一会儿就过去了
It will go away.
好的 谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
再见
Bye.
这些议员一下子都忙起来了 也真是搞笑
Funny how all these senators are suddenly very busy.
真正的原因我们心知肚明
We all know why that is.
好吧 现在的形式很严峻
Okay, so it's not great.
那一千五百万能帮我们走到现在
The 15 million helped us get this far,
但却不足以帮助我们
but it doesn't last long when you're fighting
和国会最富有的团体相抗衡
the richest group on the Hill.
直接说正事吧
Let's get to the point.
到最后投票的时候 我们究竟能拿几票？
How does it shake out when it comes to the vote?
我们之前跟他们相差不多 但根据最近的情况推断
We'd run them close. But by latest projections,
到最后我们应该会少四到七票
we'll be between four to seven votes short.
今晚也没什么可做的了
There's nothing more we can do tonight.
莉斯 不必赶我们走
Liz, we don't have to leave.
西海岸现在还是白天
The West Coast is still awake.
我们可以和俄勒冈州联系
We can connect with Oregon.
如果我们能取得那些伐木工的支持
If we close those goddamn loggers,
今晚就能赢得五张选票
we could get it to five votes tonight.
回家休息一下吧 各位
Go home and get some rest, guys.
你们已经忙了一天了
You've done enough for today.
我等会去街上 把那些该死的印有
I'll take to the streets and rip down those
弗兰克·麦吉尔的海报都撕了
fucking Frank McGill posters one at a time if I have to.
回家吧 养精蓄锐
Go home, sharpen your knives.
明天还要苦战呢
It'll still be on tomorrow.
我们继续努力
So we keep on fighting.
不然还能怎么办
That's all we can do.
我的前妻也经常这么说
As my ex-wife used to say.
你以前是干资金凑集的
I met you running from a fundraiser.
并不需要干这种事
You could be done with all this.
你为什么不选择退出？
Why don't you quit?
退出之后干嘛？
And do what?
晚安
Good night.
喂？
Hello?
真惊讶 你居然接了
I'm surprised you picked up.
抱歉 你打错了
I'm sorry, you have the wrong number.
她经常占国会议员的便宜
She'd ply Congressmen with benefits,
免费的午餐 晚会门票 以及高尔夫周末
free meals, tickets to events, golfing weekends.
全都是由我们的客户付的钱
All paid for by our clients, via the firm.
这条线索足够了吧
Well, that right there's enough.
她一定会要求我们出示收据的
She'd make a point of invoicing them,
但没人以为自己会付钱
though they were never expected to pay.
债务部分在我们的资产负债表上并没有明确表示
The debt shows as an asset on our balance sheet.
这样我们才能适时对它进行修改
We can call it in any time we want.
你当她助手当了两年
You were her right hand for two years.
一定有什么我们遗漏了的
There's got to be something.
她的档案上为什么没出现任何名字？
Why's nobody on her files?
有很多我们的人 但其余的都被删除了
There were a ton of us, but the others got pulled out.
看样子我们很难有所发现了
It's not like we're in danger of finding anything.
你现在有什么进展？
Well, how far d'you get?
我查找了她跳槽之前
We worked backwards from her last deal
接的最后一笔单子
before she jumped ship.
他们说最好能从最近的事上
They said it'd be better if we can
找出些端倪
nail her on something recent.
- 比如？ - “西玛洛蛋糕”
- Which was?  - Shmallow Cakes.
跟税金有关
Some tax thing.
她进行到一半就终止了
She left halfway through.
我怎么记得是叫什么棕榈油
I thought it was the palm oil thing.
棕榈油？
Palm oil?
能多益税金
Nutella Tax.
等一下
Hold on.
印尼？
The Indonesians?
我怎么不记得了
I don't remember seeing that.
你在找什么？
What are you looking for?
杜邦先生
Mr. Dupont,
她违反了参议院道德准则
she's in breach of Senate Ethics rules.
我们有证据
We can prove it.
这段时间你的状态不是很好啊 罗恩
Things not looking so good for you this cycle, Ron.
你要问我的话 我觉得你需要多看看付费电视
You ask me, you're gonna need a lot more paid media.
我没问你
I didn't ask you.
快想想谁能帮你搞定那些电视节目？
Now, who might just be able to fund those coveted TV spots?
我是支持希顿·哈里斯的
I'm committed to Heaton-Harris,
我不能说一套
I can't vote for it with one hand
背后做一套
and choke it with the other.
你当然可以 只需要打着公正的幌子
Under cover of impartiality, sure you can.
你曾经可是名噪一时的说客
You've been a vocal critic of lobbyists in the past.
你要发起一项针对斯隆的调查
You'll lead an inquiry into Sloane's affairs
借以回应近来越来越被媒体关注的
in response to growing media pressure
她所犯下的罪行
regarding her litany of misdeeds.
举办听证会的钱 可都来自老百姓的钱包
The cost of hearings is paid from the public purse.
罗恩 我们的客户专门选定你
Ron, our clients have identified you
作为组织这场听证会的主持
as the man to pull this off.
如果你拒绝
If you decline,
我可阻止不了他们
I can't stop them from
对你实施经济制裁
blitzing you with negative finance.
除非把你榨干 不然他们是不会善罢甘休的
They won't stop until they annihilate you.
你知道“毁灭”的这个词的词根源于哪里吗？
You know the root of the word "annihilate"?
拉丁文
It's Latin.
是“不惜一切代价消灭”的意思
It means, "reduce to nothing."
他们就会这样对你 罗恩
That's what they're going to do to you, Ron.
所以你要我怎么做？拿比尔·桑福德提供的好处
So, what? I'll be taking a wedge from Bill Sandford
然后对希顿·哈里斯
and leading the attack
最具关注度的倡导者 实施全面调查？
on Heaton-Harris' most visible advocate?
一个六年级的小学生 就会划线将点连起来
A 6th grader could connect the dots.
我们可以对现有的资源进行混淆
We can create a structure to obfuscate the source.
你将得到的好处
Your big wedge will arrive
将会被分成八到十二个小块 送到你手中
courtesy of eight to 12 smaller entities
跟枪支都毫无关系
with no affiliation to guns.
你说的好处究竟有多劲爆？
How big a wedge we talking?
劲爆到
Big enough
你可以选择
to be the difference between
继续坐在美国参议员的位置上
the continuation of your duties
或者选择
as a United States Senator
让你的职业生涯毁于一旦
and the reduction of your career to nothing.
这是自从两周前
This is every hit since
布鲁·沃尔什报道后 所发表的所有讽刺文章
the original Pru Walsh hack-job two weeks ago.
我个人最喜欢的是
My personal favorite is the one
你如何通过造谣
about how you toppled
你们的学生会主席作弊
the head of the High School Student Council
将其推翻
with a fabricated plagiarism scandal.
我觉得这并非诽谤
I'm assuming that's not libelous
因为你干得出来这种事
'cause I can totally see it.
那个婊子很讨人厌的
That witch was insufferable.
我要把你从团队中开除
I'm taking you off the campaign.
什么？
What?
不是你 是她
Not you, her.
我先出去了
I'll be outside.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
只要有你在
Heaton-Harris gets colder
希顿·哈里斯就日渐衰退
every day you're associated with it.
你和斯珀林有奸情
Sperling's got the hots for you.
我连见都没见过他 这是陷害
I haven't even met him, this is a setup.
这是他们精心策划的
If they're orchestrating it,
目的就是想让我被开除
it's because they want me off the campaign.
现在 你有一场听证会要应付
Right now, you're lawyering up for a hearing.
根据印度尼西亚政府
Regarding your representation
的陈诉
of the Indonesian government.
丹 你忙吗？
Dan, are you busy?
艾伦·雅各布议员
Senator Allen Jacobs,
是被你称为“能多益税金”的资助人
the sponsor of the bill you dubbed the Nutella Tax,
他和家人乘坐头等舱 前往印尼
was flown to Indonesia first-class with his family,
住的是五星级宾馆
and put up at a 5-star hotel.
我们的审计员预估本次旅途 共花费三万美元
Our audit puts the cost of this trip at over $30,000.
他回来之后
Shortly after his return,
很快他的提案就被搁置了
the bill was pulled from consideration.
这是怎么回事？
Now, why do you suppose this happened?
据我了解 那次旅途是带有教育目的的
I understand the trip was for educational purposes.
我猜测他意识到自己的提案
I can surmise that he learned how his bill
很可能会抑制当地基础工业的发展
would have strangled a key industry,
还会使数千位
and confined thousands
农民遭受穷苦
of impoverished farmers to destitution.
他是躺在自己的私人海滩上意识到的？
From his private beach?
真相是 你的客户资助这次旅行
No. The truth is, your client funded this trip
就是想让议员撤销他的提案的
as an inducement for the senator to withdraw his bill.
- 不是这样的吗？ - 完全不是
- Isn't that right?  - Not at all.
我的客户是印尼政府
My client was the Indonesian Government.
这次旅行是由
The trip was sponsored
环境研究学院赞助的
by the Institute of Environmental Studies,
一个非盈利的组织
a 501 C-3 non-profit organization.
整个旅行也是提前
Travel was pre-approved
通过了参议院道德委员会的允许
by the Senate Ethics Committee.
你的客户向这个非盈利组织捐过钱吗？
Has your client ever donated to this non-profit?
我不得而知
I wouldn't know that.
他们的捐赠人信息是不对外公开的
I'm not privy to their list of donors.
我也没有资格安排这样的资助
Nor had I any role in arranging funding for this.
- 没有资格？ - 嗯
- No role?  - Mmm.
那是当然 因为参议院道德准则中
Of course, you couldn't have any role
明文规定 作为一个说客是严禁
because the Senate Ethics rules prevent lobbyists
私自为国会成员安排海外旅行的
from arranging overseas travel for members of Congress.
没错
Indeed.
你知道这是什么吗？
Do you know what this is?
可以给你一份复印件
Perhaps we can get you a copy.
你对这张表格熟悉吗？
Are you familiar with that form?
熟悉 这是一张私人赞助的保证书
Yes. It's a Private Sponsor Certification Form.
这张私人赞助保证书的复印件
It's a copy of the same
跟雅各布议员想要去印尼前
Private Sponsor Certification Form
必须递交给参议院道德委员会
that was submitted to the Senate Ethics Committee
并得到提前授权的那张表格
to pre-authorize Senator Jacobs' travel
是一样的
to Indonesia.
看看这张表格下面的笔迹 斯隆女士
Look at the handwriting on that form, Miss Sloane.
你能认出这个笔迹吗？
Do you recognize that handwriting?
能
Yes, I do.
那是你的笔迹吗？
Is it your handwriting?
是我的
It is.
看来我们找到问题了
Well, it seems we have a problem.
虽然这张表格是由
Even though the form was signed
一个非盈利组织签署和归档的
and filed by the non-profit,
但填写的人是你
you were the one who filled it out.
这是能够证明你
This is prima evidence
私自安排国会议员海外旅行的
that you were involved in arranging
第一个证据
overseas travel for a member of Congress.
这违反了参议院道德准则
Constituting a clear breach of Senate Ethics rules.
这就是你们的王牌？
Is that your trump card?
你们把我拖来这里
You drag me in here,
像审讯犯人一样 窥探我的隐私
wedge an endoscope up my posterior,
到最后唯一能让我归罪的东西
and all this time, the only incriminating item
就是一堆没用的文件？
you have in your possession is a filing snafu?
那监控你要怎么解释 斯隆女士？
How about surveillance, Miss Sloane?
鲁道夫先生在法庭上作证
Mr. Rodolfo Schmidt has stated in deposition
说你有意图用
that you intended to use methods
窃听和黑客技术
such as bugging and tapping
借此欺诈汉克·巴杰利议员 这是真的吗？
to entrap Senator Hank Badgley. ls this true?
我确实有过这种想法 但那只是一瞬间的事
I did, for a brief moment, intend to use such methods.
这种企图并没有得到实施
But that intention was never acted upon.
那是为什么呢？
And why was that?
因为被斯密特先生制止了
Mr. Schmidt expressly forbade it,
我相信在他的证词里应该也提到了
as he no doubt told you in his deposition.
但很显然你对实施这样的手段
But you were clearly comfortable
很是无所谓
with these methods.
在你的游说生涯中
Did you employ the tactics of espionage
是否经常雇佣间谍技术？
regularly throughout your lobbying career?
我没有
No, I did not.
那我换个问题
Then let me ask you this.
你是否授权 命令
Have you ever authorized, ordered,
或者自己对他人
or otherwise brought about
实施过任何一种手段的非法监控？
any kind of unlawful surveillance on any person?
我先提醒你 在听证会会作伪证
Let me remind you that perjury
可是项重罪
before Congress is a felony, which...
我的答案是否定的
The answer is no.
我从没授权过任何非法的监控行为
I have never authorized illegal surveillance.
这就是我想提的所有问题了
This concludes my questioning of the witness.
谢谢你 斯隆女士
Thank you, Miss Sloane.
我们还有一个证人
We have one further witness.
如果你说的不是假话
Either you just perjured yourself,
那说明你这个人 还没肮脏到那种程度
or you're not so sleazy after all.
传证人罗伯特·福德先生
The Committee calls Mr. Robert Forde.
这我可没想到
I wouldn't count on that.
主席先生 为什么我事先
Mr. Chairman, I don't recall
没有收到通知 你要传唤…
being notified of your intention to...
我们是最近
We were only recently
才找到这位证人的 波斯纳先生
able to locate the witness, Mr. Posner.
让他们开始
Let it play.
我能和我的客户谈谈吗？
A moment with my client, please?
什么情况？罗伯特·福德是谁？
What is this? Who's Robert Forde?
听着 我可以上诉…
Look, I can make a public appeal...
赶紧开始吧 该死
Let it play, damn it.
他们不达目的 是不会罢休的
They're going to get it out there one way or another.
福德先生 请举起你的右手
Mr. Forde, please raise your right hand.
你愿意庄严宣誓 你所说的话
Do you solemnly swear that you will tell the truth,
全部都是事情的真相 只有真话
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth,
否则将会受到作伪证的惩罚吗？
under pains and penalties of perjury?
- 我发誓  - 请坐
- I swear.  - Please sit.
福德先生 你能描述一下
Mr. Forde, could you please describe
你的工作是什么吗？
the nature of your work?
我有很多个工作
I got many jobs
那你现在最高收入的工作是什么？
What would you say earns you the most income at present?
我在华盛顿做社交陪同
I work as an escort in D.C.
你靠和女人睡觉赚钱？
You sleep with women for money?
我会满足客户的需求
I meet the clients' needs.
不管是什么样的
Whatever they may be.
有时 客户可能都不知道她们有什么需求
Sometimes, the client don't even know what they need.
我的一部分工作就是帮她们解决问题
Part of my job's to figure that out.
但有时你的工作要求你
But, sometimes, your job entails
实施性交换取钱财 对吧？
having intercourse for payment?
是的
Yes, sir.
你见过伊丽莎白·斯隆吗？
Have you ever met Elizabeth Sloane?
主席先生 参议院没有权利
Mr. Chairman, the Senate has no business
窥探斯隆女士的私人生活
prying into the personal affairs of Miss Sloane.
拉皮条是一种犯罪行为
Solicitation is a criminal offense.
这场听证会的作用就在于
It's well within the remit of this hearing
探讨斯隆女士
to establish whether Miss Sloane
是否有犯罪行为
has broken any laws.
福德先生
Mr. Forde.
你见过斯隆女士吗？
Have you ever met Miss Sloane?
见过
Yep.
你能指认她吗？
Could you identify her, please?
坐在那边的那个
Sittin' right there.
你们是什么关系？
What was the nature of your relationship?
我跟一个客户参加了一个晚会
a function with a client.
我想上前搭汕 但是吃了闭门羹
I tried to introduce myself, but she bucked me off.
福德先生 斯隆女士是否
Mr. Forde, have you ever
当过你的客户？
entertained Miss Sloane as a client?
没有
No, sir.
我能出具两条具有法律效应的证词
I can produce sworn statements
是出自卡弗酒店的两位员工的
from two employees of the Carver Hotel,
他们都说看见斯隆女士出现在大厅
to the effect that they saw Miss Sloane in the lobby
而在同一天 你在那里
on the same day that you, Mr. Forde,
也接受了预约
held a reservation there.
我再问一遍
I ask again.
你是否出于金钱交换 取悦过斯隆女士？
Did you entertain Miss Sloane in any capacity, for profit?
没有 先生
No, sir. I did not.
谢谢你 福德先生
Thank you, Mr. Forde.
你可以走了
You're dismissed.
诉讼程序的结果将会在明天公布
These proceedings will conclude tomorrow,
斯隆女士的情况会交由参议院道德委员会
when Miss Sloane is referred to the Senate Ethics Committee
做最后的评判
for their judgment.
真不相信那群混蛋 居然找到那个家伙…
I can't believe those fuckers dragged that guy...
罗斯？
Ross?
我们的老朋友希顿·哈里斯怎么样了？
How's our old friend Heaton-Harris?
整个话题的热度降到了冰点
Comatose. The whole issue's gone cold.
这就是他们想要的结果
That is what they wanted.
有什么办法能让它“起死回生”
We all know what it would take to revive it.
一场地震吧
Seriously, an earthquake.
我们已经尽力了
We got closer than we had any right to.
我们明天都会到场的
We'll all be there tomorrow.
斯隆女士 请看这边
Excuse me, Miss Sloane, over here.
能问你个问题吗？
May I have a comment?
早上好
Good morning.
在我们向国会道德委员会的成员
Before referring the witness's testimony
提交证人证词之前
to the Office of Congressional Ethics,
她有权进行自我陈述
she is entitled to make a statement.
斯隆女士 你有什么想说的吗？
Miss Sloane, is there something you'd like to say?
主席先生 我的客户不想做自我陈述
Mr. Chairman, my client does not wish to make a statement.
很好
Very well.
我现在就将证词
I will now read the referral
提交给道德委员会的成员…
to the office of Congressional Ethics...
议员 我有话想说
There is something I'd like to say, Senator.
我一直被媒体 和这场听证会
I have been censured by the press and by this hearing
责备为
as a parasite
美国民主的寄生虫
on American democracy.
他们暗讽我引导枪支管制的
It's insinuated that I led the fight
运动只是为了自身事业的利益
for increased gun regulation in the interest of my career.
但有时我们行动 并不是为了自己
Sometimes we act, not for ourselves,
而是出于最简单最纯粹的理由
but because we believe plainly and simply
那就是我们相信这么做是对的
it is the right thing to do.
斯隆女士 这和我们昨天讨论的话题有关吗…
Miss Sloane, is this pertinent to the discussions we...
我有权说我想说的话 议员
I understand I have the right to say what I wish, Senator.
那你继续
Proceed.
我相信希顿·哈里斯法案
I believe the Heaton-Harris Bill
就是正确的事
is the right thing to do.
但同时我又意识到
But I also recognize
这并不是驱使我前进的动力
that this wasn't what motivated me.
当我被给予这个团队的领导职位
When I was offered a position on the campaign,
我被所面临的的挑战所吸引
I was in thrall to the challenge.
我做出的决定是基于我想获胜的欲望
My decision to accept was based on my desire to win.
获得前所未有的胜利
And to win bigger than I ever had before.
但很显然我的一些行为已经越过了
It's clear that my behavior has fallen well short
可接受的道德规范
of acceptable ethical standards.
因为自己的偏执 我的越界行为
I've crossed lines with devastating consequences
已造成了毁灭性的伤害
in the service of my obsession.
我背叛了和我最亲近的人
I've betrayed the people closest to me.
把他们的生命置于危险之中
I've endangered lives.
比起什么填写文档的违规行为
I deserve censure for this
我更愿意因为这些事而受到惩责
far more than for any filing irregularity.
当提到希顿·哈里斯法案的时候 我希望
When they consider the Heaton-Harris Bill, I wish
国会的每个成员
that each member of Congress
都能追随榜样的力量 我说的不是自己
would follow the example set, not by me,
而是坐在我身后的这群人
but by the group of people that sit behind me.
他们为自己所坚持正确的事情
Who have made great sacrifices
付出了太多 也牺牲了太多
in the name of doing what they believe is right.
我希望国会成员投票的时候
I wish that those members would use their votes,
想的不是他们自己的政治利益
not in the interest of their political advancement,
而是他们心中所坚信 对自己国家有好处的东西
but for what they believe is right for their country.
但我知道我的希望要破碎了
But I know my wishes are wasted.
因为这一切是不会发生的
And that this will never happen.
因为我们的政府腐败了
Because our system is rotten.
现在的生存之道并不会奖赏那些
It doesn't reward honest politicians,
凭良知投票的 正直的政治家
who vote with their conscience.
它只会奖赏
It rewards
卑鄙小人
rats
那些为了能分一杯羹
who are willing to sell out their country
而愿意出卖自己国家的人
to keep their noses in the trough.
恕我直言
Make no mistake.
这些卑鄙小人才是美国民主
These rats are the real parasites
真正的寄生虫
on American democracy.
我早就预想到 一旦我们为希顿·哈里斯法案
I anticipated if we had sufficient success
争取来足够的选票
in lobbying for the Heaton-Harris Bill,
就会有人想
there may be
对我实施人身攻击 或信誉攻击
an assault against me personally,
来阻止我们的势头 或者破坏我们的公信力
to stall our momentum and to damage our credibility.
游说在于先见之明
Lobbying is about foresight.
在于分析对手将会采取的计划
About anticipating your opponent's moves
然后再制定相应的应对办法
and devising counter-measures.
我想跟你谈谈我未来的发展
I'd like to discuss my future.
现在不是时候 小可爱
This is hardly the time, cookie.
最后的赢家总会比对手多留一手
The winner plots one step ahead of the opposition,
并在对方亮出王牌后 再拿出自己的杀手锏
and plays a trump card just after they play theirs.
事实上 现在正是时候
Actually, it is the time.
关键就在于你要
It's about making sure
让他们大吃一惊
you surprise them.
这他妈是什么？
The fuck is this?
而他们的一举一动都在你的预料之中
And that they don't surprise you.
我的辞职信
My resignation.
我更适合学术界
Academia's more my scene.
当我离开科尔 克拉维茨 和沃特曼的时候
When I left Cole, Kravitz, and Waterman,
我在他们的队伍中 安插了眼线
I retained an operative of mine in their ranks.
听好 简
All right, Jane.
联系鲁道夫·施密特 告诉他
Contact Rodolfo Schmidt and tell him
我们一共有六个人会过去
there is a total of six coming over.
谁说我要去了？
Who says I'm coming?
一场捏造指控的听证会
A plan was hatched to
在某个枪支管制反对派的命令下
bankroll a trumped-up hearing
就这么开始预谋了
at the behest of the gun lobby.
一定有我们遗漏的东西
There's got to be something.
真惊讶 你居然接电话了
I'm surprised you picked up.
抱歉 你打错了
I'm sorry, you have the wrong number.
她违反了参议院道德准则
She's in breach of Senate Ethics rules.
我们有证据
We can prove it.
我开始监视乔治·杜邦
I placed George Dupont under surveillance
发现他和一名国会议员见面
until he met with a member of Congress
很遗憾 这位议员道德沦丧
who exhibited sufficient moral bankruptcy
和他勾结在一起 设了这个局
to collude with such a plan.
去吧
And go.
那个人就是
That member was
罗纳德·迈克尔·斯珀林议员
Senator Ronald Michael Sperling.
注意秩序
Order.
这个平台不是给你
This is not a platform you can use
发表这种恶意指控和诽谤的
to make malicious, defamatory accusations...
在浏览器中输入以下地址
Input the following address into your browser.
“193点184
193-dot-184
点216点449”
dot-216-dot-449.
下载一个名为“地震”的文件
Download a file named "Earthquake."
我不能嘴上说一套
I can't vote for it with one hand
背地里做一套…
and choke it with the other...
快去准备车
Get the car.
鉴于以上陈诉 本次听证会休庭
In light of these allegations, this hearing is adjourned.
让开 让开 让开
Back up, please. Back up. Back up.
[一个有着坚定信仰的说客 这种信仰不仅存在于对自己取胜的能力]
[对于我的无私付出 彼得森怀亚特的回报是0元]
[马里兰 安德森市 联邦惩教所]
[十个月后]
你居然愿意出来
I'm surprised you showed.
我听说很多人来看你
I hear I'm not the only one
都被你拒绝了
whose visits you've been refusing.
你看上去气色不错
You look good.
如果你没有老二 监狱不算是个坏地方
Prison's not so bad if you don't have a penis.
我们不会在别人身上发泄 自己解决就行了
We don't shank each other, we form self-help groups.
监狱里有卖润唇膏的地方
There's a black market in lip gloss.
嗯
Hmm.
为什么同意见我？
Why this time?
他们告诉我 这次是公事
They told me it was business.
没错 额…
Yeah. Um...
关于斯珀林和杜邦的听证会
Now that the Sperling and Dupont hearings
已经提上了日程
are on the schedule,
我在帮你申请提前释放
I'm petitioning for an early release.
你看上去也很精神
You look good, too, by the way.
谢谢
Thank you.
你只需要再待四个月 最多六个月
I think we are looking at four, maybe six months.
你计划了整件事
You instigated the whole thing.
将自己全副武装起来
You weaponized yourself,
跟美国国会大厦的人来个正面对峙
brought the roof of the US Capitol
结果弄得两败俱伤
crashing down on your head.
为了什么 就为了一个枪支法案？
For what, a gun bill?
- 这很有效 不是吗？ - 祝贺你
- Worked, didn't it?  - Well, congrats.
罪犯现在买枪
Criminals must now endure the hassle
都只能去黑市买了
of procuring their guns on the black market.
这样断送自己的前程 真的值得吗？
Was that really worth your career?
如果你把因为工作而自杀 和断送自己的工作
Career suicide is not so bad when you
两者进行比较 就不会觉得这有什么大不了了
consider the alternative is suicide by career.
我的医生会告诉你
My doctor would tell you
我服刑表现很好的
I've served my interest very well.
嗯
Hmm.
谢谢你来看我 丹尼尔
Thanks for coming, Daniel.
我很好奇
I'm curious.
你签署的那个文件？
Your little filing snafu?
你是故意在上面签字的
You filled out that form deliberately.
那也是你计划的一部分 给他们设下圈套
That was you, throwing them a bone.
如果没有那个文件 也不会推动他们举办听证会
Without it, they would have nothing to incite the hearing.
你没有义务回答这个问题
And you're under no obligation to answer that.
而且整件事你完全没有
And you neglected to mention this
告诉团队的成员 是因为…
to any of your team because...
至少需要五年的信任
Five years minimum.
我会再来看你的
I'll be seeing you.
斯隆女士